August 25th, anul stelar 2148
Supplies for the Spearhead Squadron
in the 1st Combat and 1st Defense Ward?
August 15th, anul stelar 2148
Maior, ce este în acea cutie?
M-Muniție specială.
Ce este cu adevărat în ea?
Muniție specială.
Încă puțin... Încă puțin la dreapta.
Stop!
Thank you for your hard work, Ma'am!
Ți-ar plăcea să ni te alături la festivități, dșoară maior?
Initiate ID confirmation.
Maior Vladilena Milizé.
Eastern Theater 1st Combat Ward,
1st Defense Squadron Command and Control Officer.
Activez Para-RAID.
Sincronizare cu Procesoarele escadronului Vârf de Lance.
Whoa!
Look at that!
If it's hard, you should just quit.
We can handle ourselves without you.
Nothing really changes
if we don't have a control officer.
Locotenent Kukumila...
Hearing you freak out even though you're
not even on the battlefield is distracting.
Doesn't it get to you and everyone else?
Acele voci?
Doare!
Mami!
Oh, haide. Fii mai atent.
Micuțule.
Chiar și fără abilitatea lui Shin, Procesoarele aud mereu strigătele camarazilor lor care mor.
Să mori instant când îți explodează Distrugătorul este cel mai bun mod.
We've all seen our friends get their limbs
blown off, their faces ripped to shreds,
their bodies burned all over, or their
stomachs ripped open with guts pouring out,
screaming in pain as they died.
În comparație cu asta, vocile celor morți sunt o nimica toată.
For us, the thought of dying
at any time is not unusual.
Good evening, everyone.
Coming in loud and clear, Major.
Sorry, it's a little stuffy with only us guys here tonight.
Locotenent Shuga?
Ei bine, unde este căpitanul Nouzen?
Did something happen during today's battle?
No, he's just sleeping. He said he was tired.
I see.
It happens once in a while.
I... Well, we don't really know for sure,
but I'd bet it's exhausting
hearing that 24 hours a day.
Because of the voices of the Legion?
There's no point in you worrying about it.
It's just the fact that he's out here. It happens.
It's not just the Captain,
you're all being strained as well.
After taking all these casualties.
Yeah.
You haven't received a single
replacement since I've arrived.
I'll make sure it happens.
I'll do everything I can to make it a top priority.
Lieutenant Shuga?
Yeah, that'd be good.
Your unit is defending our most important base.
Replacing your losses should have the highest priority.
Until then, I'll continue to request reinforcements
from the surrounding units.
So please, hang in there a bit longer!
Yeah.
Well, I'll leave it to you. I guess.
Of course.
August 16th, anul stelar 2148
So you decided to overstep your position and
complain directly to me, Major Milizé?
Sir, I can't wait any longer for replacements
for the Spearhead Squadron.
I'll do anything to help them,
even beg you for aid.
I've gone to every department for help, but—
The resupply and Processor replacement plans
for the Eastern Theater are a settled matter.
I've already informed them of your request.
You're probably unaware
since this is an internal matter.
Really?
We're finally getting replacements?
So do your duty as best you can.
Are you ready for the
Revolution Festival party?
Attend the party in a proper dress.
Isn't that the real job for a
daughter of the Milizé family?
Understood.
August 25th, anul stelar 2148
Lena, listen...
Why did you think
that dress was a good choice?
It's pure black, like a mourning dress.
It's wonderful, isn't it?
Thanks to this, nobody's asked me to dance.
Sure this party is boring and a waste of time.
But that doesn't mean you shouldn't dress up.
Well, I think this looks nice enough for me.
That's not the issue...
What's wrong?
One of my fiancés is over there.
The one who sent me those fancy new sweets.
See you later, Lena!
Major.
Is something wrong, Captain Nouzen?
Is it the Legion?
No, you didn't call at the usual time,
so I thought I'd check-in.
Is everything okay?
If you're busy, I can contact you later.
It's fine.
Sorry, I usually call around this time, right?
What's wrong?
I wanted to let you know that
the special ammunition arrived.
It got there safely, huh?
Yes. Thank you for the fireworks.
It's the Revolution Festival after all.
You saw them with your brother
and parents before, right?
I'm sure the others have similar memories.
The Revolution Festival tradition, huh?
Can you see the fireworks
from the Palace Lune?
Let's see...
I can.
But the sky's too bright.
I'm sure your fireworks are beautiful.
The night is dark, and the air is clean.
I wish we could see them...
Let's all watch the fireworks
in the 1st Sector together someday.
I'm sure you'll laugh.
I don't remember them being that bad.
Then see for yourself.
When the war's over...
When your term's over,
we can all watch them together.
I wish Lieutenant Irma and the others
could've seen them, too.
Sorry, my timing was bad again, huh?
No, this is the first time we've been able
to give them a proper gun salute.
I'm sure Daiya and the others would be happy.
They never liked getting sentimental.
I see.
And...
Anju was finally able to cry, earlier.
She's the type that keeps things bottled up,
so I'm grateful for that too.
She'll never forget about Lieutenant Irma.
None of us will.
You remembered my brother after all, right?
That made me happy.
Because I wasn't able to remember him.
Captain Nouzen...
Major, could you please, not forget us?
Of course I won't.
But...
Before that, I won't let you die.
I won't let anyone else die.
August 25th, anul stelar 2148
Hey, Eighty-Six.
This one, too.
It's a present from your master, supposedly.
As if a pig deserves a present
from a human...
How much did you have to beg
to get her to sign off on this?
We're busy with the festival, too.
Special Ammunition
What's this?
What's up, Shin?
What is this?
Fireworks?
So many...
From the Major? Wow!
Hey, Anju, um...
What is it?
I'm wondering if we should
stop talking to her already.
Like, she's sending us presents and all now.
Are you worried about her?
No! Why would I be worried about her?
But, um...
She wasn't scared of Shin...
But, it's the least we could do.
That's all.
Shin and Raiden, the others...
They're all keeping quiet about it.
If we told her, she'd probably stop calling.
And that'd be better for all of us.
Yeah...
I remember what Kaie said to her...
She's not a bad person,
so she shouldn't get involved with us.
I think that's why Shin and Raiden
can't bring themselves to say it.
They think it'd hurt her.
Anju, are you okay?
With what?
You've never taken a shower
with someone else before.
I think it's okay now, honestly.
It's just the two of us.
There's no need to hide it.
Daiya... said I had pretty hair
when we first met.
He knew I was growing my hair out to hide it,
but he asked if I was growing out my hair
because it was so pretty.
Daiya's gone now.
So I think it's silly to keep worrying about it.
What about you? Don't you want to tell her?
No.
I don't think it's my place to say it.
Even if we die, he'd take us there.
By the hands of our beloved reaper.
I'm sure he'd bring me there. But...
But then, what about Shin?
Who will carry his heart?
August 27th, anul stelar 2148
Undertaker, report in.
All personnel are ready to begin the attack
on the Legion forward base.
Don't forget. The base is a decoy.
Watch for the ambushers in the surrounding area.
Once we've lured them into the open,
Second Squad of Fourth Platoon will open fire.
A-Analysis complete!
Firing position is 120 kilometers east-northeast.
Estimated muzzle velocity is...
4,000 meters per second?
It's an ultra-long range artillery cannon.
One we've never seen before!
I'm calling off the mission!
Retreat, please! Retreat!
Roger.
Seems like we were able to shake them.
I-I'll get you more personnel!
I'll make it happen today!
Major.
This doesn't make any sense!
The General even said
that they're planning to bring—
Major Milizé!
Everyone, you're okay with it, right?
Yeah.
W-What's going on?
Major, you've done enough.
Nothing you do will change a thing.
Captain Nouzen, what are you saying?
No replacements are coming.
Not a single one. Ever.
We're going to be wiped out.
This is an extermination unit.
W-What are you saying?
The "replacements" you were just talking about
are the Processors that will come after us.
She means, "After we're killed."
We've just received some brand-new Juggernauts.
Those are for them.
The white pigs don't intend to let a
single Eighty-Six out of the 86th Sector.
We're enlisted under the guise of
"Five years and you're free."
Then they get us killed.
They really are pigs. It's terrible.
That... That's impossible!
The vast majority of Processors die
before their term is up.
So it doesn't matter what you promise.
The problem is when you have guys like us,
who manage to survive on the
battlefield against all odds.
The longer we survive, the smarter we get.
For the other Eighty-Six, it's as if we're heroes.
They can't afford the possibility
of us leading a rebellion.
So, we're sent to the front with the worst fighting,
So we become casualties.
And if we somehow survive,
we end up here.
The 1st Combat Ward, 1st Squadron, Spearhead.
The point of this unit is
to make us fight to the death.
This is the end of the line for us.
We'll all die here.
Only after the last one is dead
will replacements come.
The next group, awaiting their own executions.
So we're not forcing you to protect us
but to kill yourselves?
That's nothing but slaughter!
Did you all know...
Yes, I'm sorry.
Since when?
From the start.
Nobody who went to war,
my sister nor anybody else, came back.
And we weren't allowed out of the camps.
We all knew from the start
that white pigs don't keep their promises.
If you knew, then why did you fight?
Why not run...
or try to get revenge on the Republic?
Revenge would be simple.
We'd just sit back
and let the Legion through.
We'd die, of course,
but we'd take the white pigs with us.
Then why?
Until I was twelve, an old
Alba woman in the 9th Sector looked after me.
Shin was raised by an Alba priest,
who refused to give up his land
and was sent to the camps.
Theo told you before about his captain.
Kurena knows the very worst of the Alba.
Of course, we all know how awful
the white pigs can be, but...
There are also people like Kaie,
who were abused by other Eighty-Six
because of the color of their skin.
Anju, Haruto, and Shin have some white pig
or imperial blood. They're the same.
There are scum like that
among the Eighty-Six, too.
And there were a lot of proud Eighty-Six
who fought to the very end.
Even if most Alba are scum,
there are some who couldn't
let us die for no reason.
And neither are the Eighty-Six all good people either.
And so we all decided which we wanted to be.
Just because scum treats you like scum,
you're the same scum if you return the favor.
If the only two paths are to die
fighting the Legion or to die giving up,
we'll survive to the last moment
and go down fighting.
That's the reason we fight.
That's our pride.
If that means protecting the white pigs,
well, that's not ideal,
but it's fine with me.
Even if you know that in the end, you'll die?
What idiot would tie a noose today knowing they'll die tomorrow?
Even if you know you're going to the gallows,
you can choose how you're going to climb up there.
We've made our choice, of our own will.
After that, all we have to do is to live.
Eastern Theater 16th Combat Ward 1st Squadron "Falkes"
Să mergem.