Colonel Milizé!
April 13th, anul stelar 2142
Tată!
Dacă mai e cineva în viață, acoperiți-vă urechile și puneți-vă la pământ!
Ești bine?
Patrulare încheiată.
Mă întorc la bază.
Vrei?
Mă gândeam că ceva dulce ar fi mai ușor de mâncat.
Sau poate nu-ți place ciocolata?
Bun.
Tata...
a spus că le facem lucruri oribile celor din Districtul 86.
Deci de ce m-ai protejat?
Ei bine...
Suntem cetățeni ai Republicii. Ne-am născut și am crescut aici.
Este datoria unui cetățean să-și apere țara. Este un lucru de care să fii mândru.
Nu sunt precum acele gunoaie de care este doar gura.
Deci am ales să lupt.
Voi lupta si voi proteja această țară până la capăt.
Am un frate. Ar trebui să fie cam de vârstă cu tine.
Sunt sigur că e mare și puternic acum.
Nu-l poți vedea?
Nu, nu mă pot întoarce încă.
Mersi.
Eu sunt Shourei Nouzen. Spune-mi "Rei".
Ce nume ciudat.
Este un nume rar în această țară.
Nu ești din Republică?
Eu și fratele meu ne-am născut aici,
dar părinții noștri erau din țara vecină.
Ai avut până acum de Imperiul Giad?
Este țara care a creat Legiunea.
Nu-ți este frică să lupți?
Ba da.
Dar dacă nu lupt, nu pot supraviețui.
Deci nu mă voi lăsa omorât. Nu pot lăsa asta să se întâmple.
Trebuie să reușesc să mă întorc...
la fratele meu.
June 16th, anul stelar 2148
Ce face fratele tău acum?
Este mort.
A murit în regiunea estică acum cinci ani.
Îmi pare rău.
Este în regulă.
Îți mai amintești când m-ai întrebat ce vreau să fac după ce părăsesc armata?
D-Da.
Nu am nimic ce vreau să fac.
Dar există ceva ce trebuie să fac.
Mi-am tot căutat fratele în acești ultimi cinci ani. Neîncetat.
Te referi la cadavrul său?
Nu.
June 24th, anul stelar 2148
'Neața, Lena.
'Neața.
Este așa de bună!
Știu, nu?
Crema este artificială, dar căpșunile sunt naturale.
Oh, așa este.
Vrei să mergem să ne căutăm rochii săptămâna viitoare?
Pentru Festivalul Revoluției.
Este deja acel moment al anului?
Chiar crezi că trebuie să merg?
Desigur.
Toți croitorii buni vor fi deja luați dacă nu te vei mișca repede.
Scuze, am fost puțin ocupată recent.
Ai fost destul de distantă în ultima vreme, Lena.
Dacă te uiți după o rochie, de ce nu inviți un domn să meargă cu tine?
Am auzit că ai întâlnit
un alt potențial partener.
Oh, Rudolph?
Era drăguț.
Tocmai ai spus un lucru bun despre cineva?
Asta înseamnă că în sfârșit...
Nici gând.
Adică, uită-te la el.
Are cinci ani.
Indiferent cât de atractivă este averea familiei mele, asta e puțin cam mult...
Why did you put up all the photos
from your past prospects?
My team did it as a joke.
So I won't forget, they said.
Lena, are you sure you're not tired?
Your face is a mess.
Is it?
You're using the Para-RAID too much.
I told you that sharing sensory data puts a lot of stress on the brain.
It's just that I pulled an all-nighter
analyzing combat data.
I know I've said this before,
but there's no point in doing
any favors for the Eighty-Six.
So don't you think it's okay to attend the party?
June 30th, anul stelar 2148
What if a battle starts during the party?
We'll be fine.
I mean, who puts on a party during wartime anyway?
Whatever happens within the walls is irrelevant to us.
We appreciate the analysis
of the enemies you provide,
but it's not something that needs
to take up all your private time.
Is what I'm doing unnecessary, Captain Nouzen?
No, your high-level analysis from a theater perspective is valuable.
Your estimates of enemy force compositions
are accurate and particularly helpful.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
But you don't need
to spend all your time on it.
If you spend too much time thinking about
the battlefield, you'll end up like me.
What kind of joke is that?
Understood.
I'll go enjoy myself then.
With the stupid party,
and the stuffy dress and high heels.
The Revolution Festival?
Do you remember anything about it?
I think I remember seeing fireworks.
In a garden with a fountain,
in front of the palace.
The palace?
Did you use to live in the 1st Sector?
I don't really remember, but I believe so.
Oh, wow!
I remember going with my brother.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have...
It's fine.
Concerning my family, I can no longer
remember their faces nor their voices.
He was reminiscing that
you'd grown up big and strong.
I could tell he really cared about you.
Your brother really wanted to go home
and be with you again.
If only that were the case...
Captain, you're supposed
to be on patrol, aren't you?
Are you in your room?
I apologize.
Well, if you've decided it's not necessary,
I'll respect that, but...
I thought you'd be angry.
I'm not that much of a stuffed shirt—
Nobody will see us here.
It's fine.
Hey, stop!
Sorry, Major.
Major?
I-It's nothing!
Really, it's nothing!
Major, we're preparing to sortie.
But, they haven't sounded any warnings.
No, the Legion are coming.
Confirmed. We're ready to go at any time.
Third Platoon's also ready.
Roger.
Captain Nouzen, how did you know
the Legion are coming?
If you weren't on patrol,
how could you find them so fast?
Major, would you please cut your Para-RAID?
There are a lot of Black Sheep this time.
It'll be dangerous to remain synchronized.
Black Sheep?
If you're curious, I'll explain later.
Please cut the synchronization.
I can't observe the battlefield
if I cut the Para-RAID.
I will not.
I've warned you.
Undertaker, you're too far ahead!
They'll surround you!
Ma...
What's this?
This isn't static.
Mom!
Help me.
Help me!
It's so hot!
Mom! Mom!
No!
Major!
Major Milizé!
I'm cutting the link, Major!
I don't want to die.
Kaie?
That voice...
Mom... Mom... Mom...
Help me!
No!
Why?
Mom! Mom!
Help me!
No!
Stop it!
I don't want to die!
June 30th, anul stelar 2148
Mom.
What is this? It's not static.
Mom!
Help me! Help me!
Damn, you're more annoying than usual today!
No!
I wonder if she'll be alright...
Major! Major Milizé!
No... Make it stop...
I'm cutting the link, Major!
I don't want to die.
Shit! That was Kaie!
It can't be! We torched
her along with her juggernaut!
Help me!
They took her? Damn it!
I don't want to die.
Gunslinger:
Heading 060, distance 800.
The enemy's front rank,
the third Grauwolf from the right.
Roger.
I don't want to die.
Target silenced.
Good work today.
Thanks.
Everybody really gave it their all today.
They wanted revenge, huh?
It's a nasty thing.
But you know, I figured they'd be
burned out after the mission.
Maybe they're feeling a bit lonely.
Around this time, she'd usually...
Right.
Those Handler's never synchronize
after hearing those voices.
Guess you're off the hook for those reports.
Yes, it's fine, Major.
I'm impressed.
I'm sorry for losing control today.
Not at all.
Captain...
Those voices I heard during the battle...
what were they?
Once, I almost died.
Actually, I probably did die back then.
So that's why I can hear them.
The voices of the ghosts
who've died, yet still linger.
Ghosts?
But there were only Legion out there, right?
I think they're ghosts, too.
They no longer have a reason to exist due to the collapse of their country.
The ghost army of a collapsed country.
So the reason you know
when the Legion are coming...
Yes. It's because I can hear their voices.
Whenever they come close.
I always hear them, even when I'm asleep.
Wait, you said always.
Do you hear them now?
Not just during battle, but even now?
Goodnight!
How far away can they be?
I don't know the exact distance,
but I can sense every Legion within the Republic's former borders.
Isn't it mentally taxing for you?
I've become used to it.
It's been a long time since it started.
Since when?
And did you hear Lieutenant Kaie Taniya's voice
because she became a ghost as well?
Captain?
The Republic's government assumes
the war will end in two years, right?
How did you know?
Theo heard it from his Captain,
the one we talked about earlier.
The Legion have a hard-coded lifespan.
In a little under two years, it'll run out.
Isn't that right?
Yes.
The Legion's central processing unit
is modeled after biological brains.
That design will stop
functioning after two years.
If that particular design will stop functioning,
they simply need to replace the design
with a new one before the deadline.
Using the materials which are readily
available on the battlefield.
You can't mean...
Human brains.
Within nature, our nervous systems are much
more well-developed than the rest.
The brains of the fallen Eighty-Six which
the Republic forbids the burial of.
Brains will eventually rot,
and I've confirmed that some Legion have the same voices.
So in actuality, it's probably a
copy of the brain's structure.
Then...
Kaie's probably still out there.
So I don't think it's the same as
what you'd call a soul.
It can't be considered the original person.
We can't communicate with it.
They're copies of the mind on the brink
of death; their final moments.
They're the phantoms that
take the form of the Legion.
And those are the Black Sheep?
Yes.
The haunted Black Sheep that hide among the White Sheep.
Of course, nowadays, the Black Sheep are more common now.
Major, you're going to lose this war.
What do you mean?
The Legion using the new design aren't at risk of shutting down in two years.
But what about the Eighty-Six?
The only ones left are children,
and they're already being sent to the frontlines.
We'll all be dead soon.
When that happens,
are the Alba able to fight?
The Alba that pushed all military service
and death onto everyone else?
Well...
They can't.
But there are fewer Legion now!
They've been reduced to less than half of what they were a few years ago.
You mean the observable forces.
It's true that the number of Legion
on the frontlines has decreased.
But that's only because they've
relocated their forces to the rear.
They're conserving and building up their forces?
There's no way. The legion
don't have that kind of intelligence.
They shouldn't.
But that's why you've overlooked it.
What do you mean?
The heads that the Legion obtain,
are more often than not
damaged in one way or another.
But the Black Sheep are still more intelligent than normal Legion.
Now imagine if they retrieve an undamaged brain.
Is that possible?
Previously, the Legion were only capable
of taking simple direct orders.
But the ghost commanders can think
for themselves and take command.
We call them Shepherds,
and they lead armies that are
unrivaled among the Legion.
Wait. This isn't a hypothesis?
They already exist?
Can you hear their voices?
I can.
The commanders' voices are especially clear.
Yes, there's one at the
rear of 1st Combat Ward.
But, if the Republic were to fall, that would still be a few years
after you've all been wiped out, right?
Yes. That'll be the case.
So we just need to
wipe out the Legion before then.
Let's win. I'll help alongside...
No. I'll have to try my hardest.
I'll analyze the enemy. Come up with plans.
Everything I can do.
Captain Nouzen...
Your term of service is up this year, right?
So let's win before then, and both survive.
You're right.
Can we call it a night?
It's lights-out here.
Sorry for keeping you up late.
Goodnight.
Este numai vina ta!
Voi veni după tine curând,
frate mai mare.
Până la capăt.