December 17th, Stellar Year 2144
Brother...
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
No matter what happens I'll never forget your voice
anata no koe wo wasure wa shinai darou
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
Swept up and scattered by the wind
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
Swept up and scattered by the wind
kaze ni fukarete chirijiri ni natte
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
shou
I can't see the future in your reflectionless eyes
sono konkontaru suishoutai ni wa utsuranai mirai mirai
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
A flower blooms only to be crushed
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
fuminijirareru dake no hana
No matter how hard I wish nothing ever changes
aigan shitemo konganshitemo kawaranai yamou
A flower blooms only to be crushed
fuminijirareru dake no hana
fuminijirareru dake no hana
A flower blooms only to be crushed
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
That's you, that's the person I see
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Bystanding, revolting, willful ignorance
boukan shiteiru zouhan shiteiru minai furishiteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
That's you, that's the person I see
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
That's you, that's the person I see
sonna anata wo boku wa miteiru
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
an
shin
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
We're all guilty in the end
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
yarukoto wa onaji sa
Don't worry, ease up why don't you
anshinshinayo bokutachi minna itsudatte
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
We're all guilty in the end
yarukoto wa onaji sa
July 27th, Stellar Year 2148
It's hot!
It's so hot!
Stop it. You're making me feel hot too!
It's hot, though.
Summer's here.
I'm stripping!
No, you aren't!
You know what they say,
"More thought, more hot" or whatever.
You're starting to sound like Kaie...
More hot... with Shin?
Here we go! Thats the spot!
Oh, that's where we watched the flowers! How nostalgic.
Isn't that the first thing we did after being deployed?
Would you like to dance again, Anju?
The battle's about to begin, Daiya.
Okay...
April 5th, Stellar Year 2148
I'm from Luskinia.
I'm from the same unit as Shin.
Set it down there.
Got it.
What unit are you from?
Scale. You?
Luskinia.
And you, Mr. Daiya?
You can call me "Daiya." I'm from Claymore.
And how many years have you been in?
It's my fourth year.
Same as me.
Seems like most of us fourth-years.
That's the one thing that's equal among us.
You've got your eyes on any of the girls?
You're asking right after we've met?
What about her? You two seemed to get along.
No! I'm not telling.
Why not? You like keeping secrets?
No more keeping secrets from us.
That's right. Daiya does nothing
but stare at Anju all day.
It's obvious he likes her.
Sounds like y'all are having some fun!
Daiya, you're embarrassing us.
Shut up and help me out here!
Hey! Sounds like Daiya wants to talk to Anju!
Excuse me? Theo?!
Give me a break!
Did you call me, Daiya?
No, it's not like that.
Then what's it like?
Well, it's just kind of a sausage-fest
over here, so I thought...
Hey, speaking of sausage-fests,
I heard the craziest thing.
What?
There's some rich girl
who's working as a Handler.
Wow, sounds interesting! Tell me more!
She's obviously a really hot pig princess!
With huge tits, too!
Since she's a pig, after all.
She's a white pig. It's only natural.
Like this?
I could see her with a
big pink rose on her back!
And I bet she talks
all prim and proper, too.
She'll greet you with,
"And a fine morning to you!"
And says "very well" instead of "yes."
I can tell you for sure
I'd snap at her in the first 30 seconds.
No, we don't know that.
She may be a frail little girl who's never held
anything heavier than a knitting needle.
She can't handle wind or rain,
and she'll wilt in too much sunlight.
Like that?
We're talking about a soldier, right?
If she was mumbling at me
in a thin, frail voice,
I'd get pretty annoyed.
Guys, calm down.
She's probably ugly and joined the military 'cause she couldn't get married.
What are you talking about?
She's obviously a goddess.
She's descended to the land of mortals
to save us poor Eighty-Six.
Well, I don't know if she's a
kind princess or a goddess, but...
I'd like to meet her someday,
if she really exists.
Well, I can tell you she's neither of those.
She's just a white pig in the end.
Right?
Anju!
Daiya...
Commander! Are they drunk or something?
I don't know.
There's nothing in those cups but water, right?
Yeah, it's water.
Well, looks like they're having fun.
Isn't that fine?
It's more like, you don't care.
People pick up these kinds of things.
I guess so.
Originally, people who were going off to battle
hated the cherry blossoms.
The flowers have a short lifespan.
They all bloom at the same time
and fall at the same time.
They leave the branches behind easily,
as if there's nothing holding them back at all.
But I like the way they're so bold.
Look, I made it my mark.
What's your mark?
There's a story behind it, right?
I think so.
You think?
It wasn't mine to begin with.
Hey, you two lovebirds!
You need to enjoy yourselves
while you've got the chance!
If you can't laugh anymore, you lose, right?
Right!
That's right.
I was worried there might be a Legion attack
while we were out here.
I'm glad there wasn't.
I told you! He can always tell!
He's the headless Reaper
of the Eastern Theater.
I heard the rumors,
but I guess they're true.
I heard you're looking for your missing head.
If I pull that scarf off, then...
You don't have a head?
That's why the skeleton mark has no head!
I get it!
Well, let's make the best of our next
six months, Reaper.
Glad to have you!
Gwad to hawve you...
Glad to have you as well, Shin.
Sir Reaper.
You, too.
You're sure popular.
I'm counting on you.
That's not like you at all.
Is it going to rain?
Look, shooting stars!
No way! No way!
Shooting stars?
Where?
Don't go chasing after them.
You're not a kid!
Me, too!
It's been four months since then, huh?
There are a lot of fewer of us.
The only number that hasn't gone down
is the one on Kujo's blackboard.
I wish time would just stop.
That'd be nice.
I'm afraid it won't for the next two months.
Sorry I'm late.
Beginning coordination mission.
Um, Captain, today...
Oh, are you scared, Major?
If you're scared, why not quit?
Major, if it's too much, you don't have to.
I'm fine!
I'll do what I can until the very end!
Got it.
Skorpions. Incoming artillery fire.
They're really getting in the way!
Wait, aren't these Skorpions
from a different unit?
There's just too many of them!
They must've figured out that
we can anticipate their moves.
Guess they're planning to level
all the ambush points
then finish us off with Löwes
once our cover is gone, huh?
That's a lot of effort for a bunch of guys
in aluminum coffins like us.
I'm so happy I could cry!
If only we had artillery as well...
Burnt Tail!
Can anyone from Sixth Platoon assist?
Not now, we're pinned down by artillery...
With this landscape, if we go now...
Daiya, wait!
I've got this!
Black Dog, get away from there!
Black Dog!
Anju...
I'm on my way, Burnt Tail!
I can fire from above!
They'll shoot back at you, Gunslinger.
Laughing Fox, can you circle
around from downstream?
March Hare could, but...
Like hell I'm ending up as scrap metal!
Make it in time!
I'm counting on you,
Reaper.
Burnt Tail!
Burnt Tail...
Damn it...
March Hare, come back.
Snow Witch, take over command from Black Dog.
Can you do it?
Yes, leave it to me.
Major.
Yes?
If I told you to cut your Para-RAID,
would you?
Is that...
You've never seen a person get shot, right?
What do you mean?
I can't let Daiya become a Legion.
If you think you can't handle it,
just cut the link.
No...
This is all I can do,
it's my responsibility as a Handler.
Thank you for the meal.
I'll get it.
I'm fine, it's light.
I'm just fine.
Really?
Really, I'm fine.
Right, Kitty?
Let's play darts.
So we finally lost Daiya and Lecca, too.
Out here, it's only a matter of time.
Yeah.
You'll still fight,
even if you're the last one left.
Not until you can dig your brother a grave?
It's all I can do.
My brother hasn't forgiven me.
He still blames me. That's why...
You're still obsessed with your brother's head.
I guess you really are a Reaper
in search of a missing head.
Shin.
It's your fault.
Everything. It's all your fault!
That Mom and Dad died.
The fact that I'm about to die.
It's all...
All because of your sin!
Shin!
It's good.
Thanks, Annette.
Did you use real eggs?
Artificial.
The strawberries are real.
July 27th, Stellar Year 2148
Sorry, there wasn't time.
No, it's fine.
I'm glad you came, though.
Happy birthday, Lena.
But your present was delivered yesterday.
Oh, you got it?
Why a rocking chair?
"Why?"
Well, you know...
I thought it'd be nice.
Actually, Nicolaus gave it to me,
but I'm never going to use it.
It seemed like someone older picked it.
You seem like you haven't been getting enough sleep.
It's perfect for a nap, right?
Annette, you keep getting guys with a big age gap.
Well, all the guys my age...
Not a chance.
They're too childish.
So, what's on your mind?
You came to ask me something, right?
Hey, Annette.
What is it?
Just hypothetically,
if the Para-RAIDs had some kind
of effect on a person's mind...
Oh, then it'd go "pop."
We'd pop the Processor's skull right open
and do a thorough exam of their brain.
Just like we were planning to do with Undertaker.
And after we're done, we'd toss it.
For Handlers, we'd give them a thorough exam,
then transfer them to another unit.
Sorry, I have to go.
Leave the cake.
I'll come back and eat it later.
Lena?
I'll make the usual cake next year.
Something like this is fine.
Thanks.
I can't let Daiya become a Legion.
Captain Nouzen has been doing that for years,
to keep his comrades
from becoming part of the Legion.
July 28th, Stellar Year 2148
Two Processors died in the last battle.
One was mortally wounded,
but it was his combat commander,
not the Legion, who dealt the killing blow.
How many machines are left?
Sixteen people.
The range of our military's artillery are
comparable to the Skorpion's howitzers.
We can support them from the rear
and save the lives of the Eighty-Six.
No, we can lessen attrition at the front lines
and defend the nation more efficiently.
Artillery needs to be reloaded after firing.
Their range would force us to
set them up in our own minefields.
And they'd be too close to the frontlines.
You're telling us
to take that risk for the Eighty-Six?
Eighty-Six can be replaced,
but Republic soldiers can't.
I can't authorize their use.
Both the military and the people
want a homeland defense
that's technologically advanced and ethical,
with zero casualties.
And the military's job is
to follow the will of the people.
But...
Lena, how many times do I have to tell you?
Stop siding with the Eighty-Six.
But, they're human...
They must be suffering.
On that topic, I have a new mission
for the Spearhead Squadron.
We've confirmed that the Legion have set up a new operational base near the frontlines.
As soon as preparations are complete,
they are to advance upon
and destroy the base.
Wait, even before we've replaced their losses?
Why don't we get replacements,
like the other units?
This base exists to support the
Legion in their advance.
If we don't strike now before it's completed,
it'll be Spearhead that suffers.
You want to save them, right, Major Milizé?
Or am I wrong?
Understood, sir.
This concludes the mission briefing.
Understood.
I'm sorry.
You haven't even received replacements
and we're already sending
you on a new mission.
It's nothing new.
We're already aware of the Legion base.
It's almost certainly a trap.
You know it's a trap,
yet you'll attack anyway?
It may be more dangerous to leave it there.
I wish we could've used the
artillery to provide support.
But I couldn't get authorization.
Oh, those things?
I've never seen them fired.
I'd be surprised if they still worked.
Is that so?
Don't worry about it.
We weren't counting on them to begin with.
Stress is bad for your skin!
Yeah.
That's all for today, then.
Try to get some rest tonight, okay?
Right, right.
Goodnight!
Bye!
Night.
Captain?
Major, are you okay?
Your voice sounds a little on edge.
Make sure you get some rest tonight.
Okay...
You can get sweets inside the walls, right?
Why not eat some and take a break?
What is it?
No...
You just sounded like your brother.
He gave me chocolate when things were bad.
You really are brothers, huh?
It's far worse for you than it is for me.
You must like sweets too,
right, Captain Nouzen?
Yes. Did my brother say that?
Yes.
What was his expression when he said it?
Was he smiling?
Yes.
He had such kind eyes.
I remember them really well.
I'm impressed you remember.
It's an important memory for me.
I'll never forget it.
Of course, this time I spend talking
to you is very important as well.
Major?
O-Okay, goodnight!
Goodnight.
One,
two,
three,
we
made
it
through
two,
three,
we
made
it
through
Four
and
five,
five,
Light up the fleeting sky
with
light
dle
it
with
light
It's unfathomable, give in and say goodbye
Heed those doubtless words
I won't forget.
ki
ke
Stand
up
and
get
a
start
up
and
get
a
start
Do what you must
no
mu
ku
ma
It’s
de
pen
ding
on
your
heart
de
pen
ding
on
your
heart
Can
take
shi
vers
of
your
scar
take
shi
vers
of
your
scar
Draw upon the ever-expanding world
Even heros will eventually fade
Raise
your
hands
up
to
the
sky
your
hands
sion
As it fades away, the Vision
sion
Guides us to the future
Trou
Trou
ble
ma
ker
How’d
you
know
’bout
my
fe
ver
you
know
’bout
No matter how young the night is
You won't find the answer here
Raise
your
hands
up
to
the
sky
your
hands
sion
Release the dimension
sion
Open up a new page
Trou
Trou
ble
ma
ker
How’d
you
know
’bout
my
fe
ver
you
know
’bout
No matter how much I love
I can't say it out loud
Will you remember me?