15 Years Ago
Acum 15 ani...
First World Collision
Intrările profețite, crăpături ale realitații care conectează lumea oamenilor cu o altă dimensiune,
au apărut dintr-odată pe întreg globul.
Fiecare armată a Pământului
a suferit o înfrângere teribilă,
fără măcar să știe contra cui luptau.
Intrările au dispărut la două
săptămâni după apariția lor,
iar pericolul părea să fi trecut.
Dar apoi...
Six Months Ago
Second World Collision
ei s-au întors.
Guvernele lumii s-au retras pe
orașele plutitoare de pe ocean.
Dar, doar o mică parte din
populație a reușit să scape.
Lumea încă este invadată de inamicii care continuă să vină în număr mare prin Intrările încă deschise.
Dar noi nu am stat degeaba.
Am dezvoltat echipamentele Hibridul Inimii, care ne permit să luptăm de la egal la egal cu inamicul.
Aceasta este echipa de top, care folosește Hibridul Inimii, din Ataraxia, Amaterasu.
Ei sunt cei mai importanți luptători ai noștri.
V-ați descurcat grozav astăzi.
Ca directoare și comandant aici în Ataraxia, sunt mândră de voi.
Surioară, vorbești serios când spui că ești și directoare, și comandant?
Și acum avem o modalitate de a face echipamentele și mai puternice.
Și mai puternice?
Vreau să vi-l prezint.
Acesta este Hida Kizuna, elev în anul 2
care se va alătura Diviziei Tactice a Liceului.
Era deja decis ca el să intre în Amaterasu odată cu venirea la această școală.
Asta este cheia victoriei noastre.
Uau!
Credeam că este genul timid, dar se pare că m-am înșelat.
Așteaptă, eu...
Ce vrea să însemne asta?!
Așteaptă puțin.
Ei bine, tu ești...
Divizia Tactică a Liceului, clasa 2-1,
și membră a consiliului de
disciplină, Hayuru Himekawa!
Ce făceai în mijlocul luptei?!
Nu-mi vine să cred!
Atât de indecent!
Dezgustător!
Și pervers!
Ăsta nu este un joc!
Împărtășind iubire și plăcere cu Hida Kizuna,
energia pierdută de echipamentul Hibridul Inimii poate fi refăcută drastic.
Acesta este Hibridul Inimii.
Hibridul Inimii...
Noile voastre ordine:
membrii Amaterasu trebuie să acumuleze putere și energie
făcând lucruri indecente cu Hida Kizuna!
Asta este valabil pentru oricine dorește să intre în divizia Amatarasu.
Odată ce ați intrat, trebuie să faceți un Hibrid al Inimii cu Kizuna.
Nu înțelegeți greșit, toată lumea!
Chiar nu aveam niciun
gând erotic în acel moment!
Eros!
Este un pervers!
EPISODE 2
Cum te poți trezi mai târziu decât mine?
Dar leneș mai ești.
C-Chidorigafuchi...
De ce?
Am venit pentru o noapte fierbinte.
Dar este dimineață.
Atunci, haide s-o numim o dimineață fierbinte, bine?
Mai bine nu. Chiar nu era nevoie să vii.
Bun, haide să începem.
Așteaptă...
B-Bun, fă un Hibrid al
Inimii cu mine chiar acum!
A-Așteaptă puțin.
De ce te grăbești atât de tare?
Hei, Hida?
Bună dimineața.
Himekawa?
Poate că au existat niște motive bune pentru lucrurile pe care le-ai făcut ieri.
Îmi cer scuze că m-am supărat pe tine fără măcar să aud ce aveai de spus.
Hida?
Voi intra, bine?
So, I know this doesn't really make it any better,
but I wanted to walk you to school...
Animalule!
Ai adus-o pe Aine în camera ta ca s-o seduci?!
Te înșeli!
Cum anume?!
Nu este ceea ce pare, Hayuru.
Eu sunt cea care sărise pe el.
Eu încercam să-l seduc ca să facă un Hibrid al Inimii cu mine.
M-Mi-a ajuns!
Neros!
Vă voi învăța pe amândoi o lecție!
Zeros.
Fetelor, vă rog, nu în camera mea!
Did you hear the explosion from the dorms this morning?
Apparently it was Himekawa and Chidorigafuchi.
That's right!
It was in that Eros boy's room!
It doesn't make any sense that he's in
the same dorm and classroom as the girls!
We're hoping that intimacy develops
between them through time spent together.
But still, you know...
Girls, it's wrong to judge someone based on
their appearance and first impressions.
Better to decide after you've seen
if he's worthy of special treatment.
How compassionate you are, Julicia!
I feel purer just hearing you speak!
Yeah, figures...
Good morning, Kizuna.
M-Morning.
Hey, perv!
Julicia Farandole is an American
military ace and a rich celebrity!
You're not even worthy of speaking to her!
Now, now. Calm down, everyone.
Hey, is what the high commander said true?
If I seek pleasure with you,
will my Hybrid Count really go back up?
I-I don't really know...
Ms. Farandole...
Call me Julicia.
Would you like to try right now?
Julicia, a classroom is a sacred place,
so I won't let you do anything indecent here!
Then it's fine as long as we're not in the classroom?
No, it's not fine anywhere!
Um...
Are you busy?
Who are you?
Sylvia Silkcut, Middle School Year 1!
The commander wants to
talk to you, Captain Kizuna!
This is the Heart Hybrid Gear research lab,
also known as the Nayuta Labs.
The basic technology behind the
Hybrid Gears was developed here.
Yeah, that's right.
That's Dr. Hida Nayuta, right?
The super-important person
who developed the Gears.
Mom...
Shikina Kei
It's Sylvia.
Enter.
Wow...
This way.
I'll introduce you.
This is the lab's director,
Chief Engineer Shikina Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Hello.
I am Shikina Kei.
You can call me Kei.
Well, don't let it bug you.
Anyway, Kizuna, I'll give you this to start with.
It's a portable terminal that also
functions as a student handbook.
Yours is special.
Tap the icons of the Amaterasu members.
This is private information!
That's why it's special.
You can see one of the listings
is for Hybrid Count, right?
When their count goes below five percent,
it becomes difficult to maintain their Gears.
Keep that in mind.
Keep that in mind?
Simple.
If you Hybrid Heart, the count will recover.
Gear energy doesn't recover naturally?
Natural recovery takes far too long.
And the energy loss in combat is huge.
So we need you and your Gear, Eros.
Our latest research shows
that Eros has a special function.
Heart Hybrid, a technique that
can rapidly restore Hybrid Counts.
It's no exaggeration to say that the fate
of humanity rests on your shoulders.
Do your job as captain justice.
Wait.
I'm captain?
Starting today, you're the captain of Amaterasu.
But that's so sudden!
I'll help as best I can!
Sylvia is going to keep me updated
on whether things are proceeding smoothly
between you and the members of Amaterasu.
Yes!
I'll do my best!
This is crazy...
Work hard. You've got a mission now.
A mission?
I'll go over the mission details again.
Your job is to gather data on a nearby
island and recover resource samples.
This is your first mission as Amaterasu's captain.
Stay sharp out there.
How can someone so indecent be our captain?!
I'll go on ahead and scope out the area!
Wait a second—
Oh, Hayuru, you're so silly.
Julicia.
Oh? What is it, High Commander?
Be careful.
Your Hybrid Count is at twenty percent.
Avoid combat as much as possible.
Don't worry. This place is safe.
Shouldn't you worry about
your little brother instead?
Doesn't seem like he's flying very steadily...
Okay, I'll go catch up to Hayuru.
They're both so fast.
Of course.
Hayuru is Japan's ace,
and Julicia is America's.
I-I see.
By the way, how good are you?
Japan's #2?
Or some foreign ace?
Don't underestimate me.
I'm the ace of the entire Earth.
Earth?
Oh no, I got it wrong.
I meant the entire universe.
The entire universe, huh?
Data recovery initiated.
It will take two hours or so to finish.
So we get our samples during that time?
Okay, let's go, Kizuna!
Make sure you escort me right.
Come on!
You're such a worrywart, aren't you, Kizuna?
Entrances only appear on land
masses above a certain size.
That means this tiny island is safe.
No, that's not it...
So, what are the specs on your Gear?
Not exactly sure how to answer that.
So that's how it is.
What's your kill score, then?
Zero.
So what, you're really a complete rookie?
Any combat experience?
The battle yesterday was my first.
Though all I did was grab Chidorigafuchi as she fell.
I didn't do anything else, really.
How many enemies have you defeated, Julicia?
About three hundred.
Three—?!
That's America's ace for you.
There's nothing amazing about me.
Julicia?
Come, let's regroup with Hayuru and Aine.
Okay.
Aine, let's go meet Julicia and—
An Entrance?!
No, that doesn't make any sense!
Equip your Gear, Hayuru!
Fire!
This is Kizuna!
Ataraxia, come in!
Shikina! Sis!
Connection Failed
Don't bother.
When an Entrance appears,
normal communications stop working.
But Gear users can talk to one another.
Aine? Hayuru?
No... why?
Julicia!
Connection Failed
Hida!
It's not working.
Hayuru, look!
What's happening?
Blade!
No way!
We're locked in?
Kizuna, go grab the others.
But then you'll be all by yourself.
You'll just slow me down!
Go!
Fine!
Eros!
Now then...
You boys ready?
Damn it!
A girl's risking her life in combat!
And I...
Julicia!
My Hybrid Count is down to six percent.
That's cutting it awfully close.
A Dragorie?
That's a Category-A Magitech weapon.
Fire!
My beam's power is dropping!
I can't move my hands...
Or my legs...
My body feels so heavy...
Wait!
My chest...
Julicia!
Kizuna!
Wh-Why?
Why did you come back?
Julicia...
Run...
Why?
Why are you doing this for me
when we've only just met?
What are you talking about?
A girl's... in danger...
Of course I have to help her.
That's the only reason he did this?
Run, Julicia!
No...
Kizuna...
Don't...
I...
No...
What is this sensation?
What's going on?
Amazing. My whole body
is overflowing with power!
So this is a Heart Hybrid?
Thank you for coming to save me, Kizuna.
Just watch.
This is my...
Showtime!
Hellfire!
This time!
What?
The Entrance is gone!
Aine! Hayuru!
Are you okay?
Julicia?
Best I've ever been!
I did a Heart Hybrid with Kizuna,
and now I'm better than ever!
Hey, Julicia...
So that means you too, Julicia?
How could this be?!
We let our guard down today.
That island increases in size as the tide goes out,
so it became large enough
for an Entrance to appear.
We missed that.
I wouldn't have made Julicia go with
such a low Hybrid Count if I had known.
After her Count got in the red zone,
she seemed to be in a lot of pain.
Are you sure you don't want to tell him, Reiri?
I think we can wait until you're ready.
You're late.
How could you keep me waiting?
Why are you here?
To do a Heart Hybrid, of course.
You don't even understand that?
I refuse to understand!
Kizuna!
Julicia?
Are your wounds okay?
What about you? Are you okay?
Yes!
All thanks to you, Kizuna.
So...
Let's do some more, okay?
I'm first, Julicia!
Oh my, Aine.
You want to do a Heart Hybrid again?
Well, I'm sure you do.
The one before was basically an accident!
Hida, this is Himekawa.
Are you feeling okay?
As a fellow Amaterasu member...
How indecent!
Neros!
I'll punish you!
Not happening.
Come on!
No fighting in my room!
Why, you...
High Commander, I've got my report!
Illustration
Shinpei Kobayashi
Kyoto, Okinawa, Akihabara!
Megafloat Japan's the perfect place
for a date, isn't it, Kizuna?
A date?
Are Julicia and Hida...?
NEXT TIME
GENTLE DAYS - MEMORIES
How indecent!