Look, everyone!
We can see it now!
Wow!
So that's Planet Vilavurs.
I'm so excited!
I wonder what kind of food we'll find!
Did I seriously forget my sunscreen?
Check this out! I made a bug net!
Cool! Let's catch some beetles!
Seriously, can you guys be any less cautious?!
All right!
Let's make our beetles fight each other!
Team B-5, camp log. First planet, Vilavurs.
Interesting!
Yeah! Prepare to face the master beetle trainer!
We must find and store 20 days' worth
of food and water on this planet.
Wonderful! Let's add stag beetles to the mix.
Stag beetles!
Cool!
I can't say excitement is
the only feeling I have,
Guys, are you serious?
but I still look forward to it!
Planet Vilavurs
Day_
Day 4_
Planet Vilavurs
Day 4 lost in
Day 4 lost in sp
Day 4 lost in space
Huh, this planet seems nice.
Shouldn't we be a bit more cautious?
Wh-What was that?
Over there!
Wow, it's big! Like a dragon!
If it attacks us, we're doomed.
Um, I was thinking.
Its head looks like a turtle.
Let's call it a Tur-Gon!
Why are you so happy to see it?
Are you stupid or something?!
Quit being scared! If they try hunting around here, we'll catch one and eat them!
If this were a horror movie,
you'd definitely be the first to die.
Augh, I don't want to deal with this!
Let's get off of this planet, and fast!
Wh-What...
I finally got to hear you speak up, Yunhua.
Badump
Don't do that, Aries!
The helmets are all on the same channel, remember?
Badump
Whoopsie, sorry everyone!
What's the deal?
So loud!
At least we know your comms are back in working order now.
That's right!
Zack was able to fix it up!
Maybe we should have kept it broken.
Ah, that was supposed to be my job.
This time, I'll do it.
I'm going to be a strong, dependable leader.
We'll split up into three teams.
Zack and Funicia, work on the ship.
Understood.
Aye aye!
Ulgar and Yunhua, you're on water duty.
The rest of us will go foraging for food.
No.
What?!
I'm not doing anything dangerous.
Well, of course there's some risk,
but I promise I'll keep my eyes peeled...
I don't trust you.
What?!
Sorry, but what kind of food should we be looking for?
Oh yeah, good question.
Nuts are usually the safest and most nutritious. Berries are second.
On the other hand, the risk of poison makes mushrooms and red plants less attractive.
Impressive, Kanata!
You said something really useful for once!
Ha, ha, ha! Follow me, comrades!
So...
Which is a nut, and which is a berry?
How should I know?! I'm sorry, okay?!
This is wonderful.
The local flora and environment appear similar to the Treepeel Spat system.
We can expect species with well-developed fibrovascular bundles!
I don't understand a word he said,
but it sounded way more impressive!
You sure know a lot about plants!
Oh no, it's just a weird hobby.
Let's just grab whatever we can find.
We can figure out if it's safe or not later.
His instructions are getting vague.
They won't attack, will they?
Flying creatures that large wouldn't fit in the deep forest.
It's— It's an alien creature!
Of course. We're in a forest after all.
Now that I actually look, they're everywhere!
They'd better not be dangerous!
Maybe they are, maybe they aren't.
Oh stop, Juliano.
Why is the hot one so crazy?
Can you please not blend in with the aliens so easily?!
You're a naughty one, Juliano...
This stick totally looks like a sword!
Mine's a spear! I call it the Luca Javelin!
What is up with the boys?
Is this just another field trip for you?
This tree is fun. It's like a trampoline!
The top side is grass-like. Is this for photosynthesis?
Let's play sumo!
How about having a healthy fear of the unknown, huh?!
Why don't you join us, Quitterie? It's fun!
Hmph.
As if.
It's like I'm the only one seriously foraging out here.
Oh, here comes Quitterie!
Interesting! A parachute-like structure, to spread the seeds in the heavy fruit!
Now's not the time to go into professor mode!
Oh hey, a star shape.
This is awesome.
Everything here
is something I've never seen before.
Hey, we can't be too relaxed.
Yeah, let's get out there and actually find some food.
Weren't you the one who suggested the sumo match?
What's wrong, Zack?
Nothing.
Looks like we got food and water.
Yeah.
As long as you don't give up, it'll work out.
Right, tomorrow let's go hunting!
Gah! No way!
Hey, no sweat!
One swift stab of the Luca Javelin will end the hunt in a flash!
Wait, huh?
You left it on the trampoline tree.
Whoops.
As long as you don't give up...
The ball!
Run!
Get to the ship!
What is that thing?!
Helmets on!
Which way is the ship?
Is it this way?
No, it's this way!
Come on!
I remember that tree!
This way!
Get past that rock, and we'll be out of the forest!
Aries, do you really remember every bit of the scenery?
I have a photographic memory.
What is that stupid sphere?!
I'm sick of this! I'm going home!
Why do I have to stay on this stupid planet?!
We're here so we can get home!
Is it possible that the sphere would take us back to McPa?
No, I don't think so.
I got a glimpse of the inside of the sphere and saw stars.
We'd probably get dumped right back into outer space.
This is the second time we've seen it.
Is it really a natural phenomenon?
I feel like we're getting caught up in something really big and scary...
He just started chowing down!
He couldn't handle the silence!
We don't even know if it's edible yet!
Are you stupid or something?!
Shut up. I'm hungry.
Up in the mountains, the biggest enemies were hunger and having too much time to think.
Was help coming? Just thinking about things we didn't know was driving us insane.
You don't know what you don't know,
no matter how hard you think!
Stating the obvious again...
But he has a point.
For now, we just have to tackle the issues in front of us to survive.
So eat up! Captain's orders.
Excuse me? Don't you dare "captain's orders" me when you totally suck as a captain!
Charce is way more suited for the job!
Give him a break, Quitterie.
Kanata, don't mind her.
If you're gonna act so bossy, do something about the Tur-Gons or the sphere!
Fine then! I'll go and catch a Tur-Gon!
What?!
Then you'll have to admit I'm captain! What then, huh?!
Kanata, you can't let that be enough to ruffle you.
I'm not!
You've gone too far, Quitterie.
You haven't changed from when we were little.
How many friends have you lost that way?
Whatever!
I don't need friends!
Not that any of these people are friends anyway!
Quitterie...
Can't we all get along?
Stop being a smart mouth! You're not even my sister!
Quitterie!
Well, that fell apart.
How far do you think Quitterie went?
Don't worry, she's not a child.
Zack, you seem to know Quitterie pretty well.
We're childhood friends, so...
Huh. Has she always been like that?
Yes.
She never knew her father, and her mother is a busy doctor who is never around.
She was practically raised by caretakers and staff, which made her selfish.
She doesn't know how to deal with people.
She also couldn't figure out how to deal with suddenly having a sister.
Suddenly?
Funi is from an orphanage,
and Quitterie's mother adopted her.
I like Quitterie.
I didn't have any siblings or friends.
I'm happy to have a pretty sister like Quitterie.
Huh? An adoption?!
What do you mean, Mom?!
I mean exactly that. A friend of mine passed away and left a daughter behind.
I've decided to bring her into the family.
Take care of her.
Take care of her? Me?
When you can't be bothered to take care of me?
When you don't love the child you already have?
Why bring home another one?
I'm Funicia.
Don't get close to me.
Nobody ever taught me how to love.
Huh? Where's Funi?
Where'd she go?
We were concentrating too much on finding Quitterie.
Over here!
Oh, it's the trampoline tree!
Guess what, guess what? There's a pretty flower here!
What's going on?
The trampoline trees grew?!
Funi!
Quitterie!
Funicia!
Hold on! I'm coming!
If it's reacting to the sunlight,
it should come back down at night...
We have to wait for that?!
We're too high up to build a bridge...
A Tur-Gon!
It's trying to get Funi!
Funicia!
Kanata!
Aim for the closest footing.
Can I reach it? Is it even possible?
He's going to jump that without anti-grav shoes?
When things seem hopeless...
Act tough!
He made it!
Good job!
Awesome!
Isn't he scared of dying? That drop is totally lethal. Who is he?
Kanata Hoshijima... I remember!
I saw a news article about him.
He's a decathlete, the sport where one person has to be able to run, jump, and throw.
No wonder he's so athletic.
That alone doesn't explain why he can make that jump.
Kanata is someone who can risk his life for his friends.
Yes!
Nice, Kanata!
Just one more!
Just hold on, Funi...
He's exhausted...
Of course. He's making so many jumps under such intense pressure.
I'm going.
Quitterie, wait!
Funi!
No!
We can't let it fly away with her!
I can't reach it from here!
Isn't there any way?
Is there...
That's the...
Luca Javelin!
The what?
Javelin throw!
Go! Kanata!
He...
He did it!
He got it!
Funi's okay too!
I'm exhausted...
Hold on!
It's just like when he saved me.
He came flying through space, and said...
"Way to hang in there."
Way...
...to...
Whoa...
What the hell?!
Just in time.
Talk about having too much confidence in yourself!
Way to hang in there.
Thanks!
Funicia!
I'm sorry! It's all my fault!
No, it's my fault. I'm sorry I went up the tree.
I saw a flower like yours, so I wanted to get it...
A flower?
Is this...
I-I'm sorry, Funici—
Funi.
Thank you, Kanata.
Huh?
I apologize for how I was back there.
No, I apologize for how I've been this whole time.
This whole time...
I couldn't say what I really meant.
I've never been able to get along with people...
You can start being honest from now on.
To your family and your friends.
I don't want to hear that from you.
What?!
Not honest...
Hmph!
That was quite impressive, Kanata!
I mean, the athletics were amazing, but you've got ridiculous nerves of steel!
Your balls have gotta be bigger than platypus eggs!
What kind of a compliment is that?
I didn't know you were a decathlete.
It's not like my job or anything, but my dad trained me.
My dad used to be an athlete who everyone thought was on track to set a new world record,
but he had to retire early due to injury.
He more or less forced his dream on me,
and I always wanted to run away.
When I met my teacher in middle school, I got interested in space exploration.
I finally cut myself free from my dad.
Then we got lost in the mountains.
If only I had more stamina, more courage...
Maybe I could have done more,
and maybe my teacher would be alive.
I begged my dad to train me again.
I don't intend on competing, though.
I'm not taking over my dad's dream.
I'm taking over my teacher's.
I also intend on going into space research.
When you need a crew for your ship, I'll be there, Kanata.
Yes, I'd like to be there too.
That's great! Sounds like you're all ready to lead this team, then!
Hold on a sec.
I'm not fit to be captain.
I took a stupid risk all on my own. If Quitterie didn't help me, I'd be dead.
Like Quitterie said, Charce should be—
Not many people can make critical decisions and act on them without hesitation.
We're all in agreement here.
I can be your second in command.
You should be captain.
All right then. Thanks for having me, guys!
Don't mention it!
Awaiting instructions!
Well then!
Let's haul this back to the ship.
What?!
Seriously, Tur-Gon meat is delicious!
I could just eat this for the rest of my life!
Me too!
Delicious!
But we may need to balance our diet over the next 20 days.
koboreta mama no ryuuseigun
An overflowing meteor shower
ichibyou ichibyou
One second, two seconds
About that... I've gathered some junk parts from around the ship,
kokyuu shite mo tsumeato wa mune wo saku yo
Just breathing makes the scars tear my heart apart
and assembled an edibility tester.
This guy's kinda incredible.
For example, if I stick it in this berry...
kata ude no netsu wa doushite sadame iro kidou wo egaite
Why does the fire in my arm paint a destiny-colored orbit?
Yummy.
Are you going for mass-market appeal with this thing?!
Wait, did you record your own voice for this?
nukumori no ame tabanetara
When I gathered the raindrops of brotherhood
sora no ao ni yurameita
They were flickering in the blue blue sky
eigou kaiki hanbunko kataku musubareta inochi
Eternal recurrence split two ways, tightly bound lives
What's wrong, Aries?
I'm sorry, that was just very funny.
kokoro tsuresatte furuete iru
As they pull my heart away, I can't stop shaking
This might be inappropriate, but I'm starting to enjoy the situation we're in.
kizutachi ni mo arigato
I'm grateful to everything, even my wounds
ruten lights kesenai konagona ginga
In this infinite, inexhaustible, fragmented universe
I lived out in the country and didn't have many friends.
noizu darake no kage ni furikaette mo
Even when I'm looking back at my blurred shadow
So I'm glad to be friends with all of you.
honto wa, honto wa, kawaritai sono jibun ga
The truth is, the truth is, I want to change
sugu soba ni irun da
That part of me is right by my side
Team B-5, camp log.
mugen bright zen sekai bokura ga fiidobakku
Looking blind, through the sky, we'll be back
We were able to leave Planet Vilavurs in just two days.
nagai tabi no kanata ni yukitsuku basho
To where our long journey will come to an end
mienai, mienai daitetai sotto hikari de
I can't see it, I can't say it, I want to embrace it
Also, we've all gotten closer to each other!
kimi no te wo nigirou
Using that light, I'll grab your hand
Kanata, there's something I need to tell you that I don't want the others to hear.
The communicator was destroyed on purpose?!
How can that be?
I took a closer look. The missing parts appear to have been cut out,
and the cuts seem very new.
So, you mean...
One of the people on this ship is behind this.