-·- · -· - ·-  ··· ···· ·· -· --- ···· ·- ·-· ·-
Original
Manga
Kenta Shinohara
SHUEISHA JUMP COMICS
Series Writer
Norimitsu Kaihou
Character Design
Keiko Kurosawa
CGI
LARX ENTERTAINMENT
CG Director
Daisuke Katou
Audio Dir.
Satoki Iida
Masaru Yokoyama
Music
Hiroaki Nobusawa
Nu... Propulsoarele nu funcționează...
Sunt complet singură aici.
Îmi este teamă!
Animation Producer
Yuji Higa
Anim. Production
Asst. Director
Yusuke Shibata
Director
Masaomi Ando
Îmi este teamă...
Să rămâi singur este înfricoșător!
Aries' Apartment
_
Day
Day be
Day befo
Day before
Day before leav_
Day before leaving_
Day before leaving ca_
Day before leaving camp
Aries!
Ești gata pentru ziua de mâine?
Desigur! Am tot bagajul pregătit și sunt gata de plecare!
Hm?
Ce este asta?
Pașaportul meu! Am uitat să-l pun!
Te voi întreba din nou.
Aries, ești sigură că ești gata pentru ziua de mâine?
Păi, desigur!
Dar tu, mamă? Te vei descurca de una singură?
Voi fi plecată pentru cinci zile...
Nu-ți face griji. Mergi și distrează-te.
Spune-mi din nou, unde se ținea tabăra?
Pe planeta McPa!
_
Mousanish Spaceport
Day_
Day of_
Mousanish Spaceport
Day of depar
Day of departure
Zborul 77 pleacă din Mousanish...
Sunt așa încântată...
Sunt așa de încântată!
Tabără...
pe o altă planetă!
Oh?
Ohmygosh!
Îmi pare foarte rău!
Ești foarte entuziasmată, nu-i așa, domnișoară?
Oh, thank you!
Tabără pe o altă planetă, spuneai? Ești cumva de la Liceul High?
Și eu am fost în acea excursie. Acum mult timp.
Serios? S-a ținut pe planeta McPa?
Da.
Cinci zile, doar elevi.
Fusese prima mea călătorie în spațiu, deci a fost puțin înfricoșătoare la început.
Dar odată ce am reușit să cunosc restul echipei,
a fost mult mai distracitv decât mi-aș fi putut imagina.
Mergi și distrează-te. Dar ai grijă, bine? Pari puțin aiurită.
Ha, ha... Nu sunt aiurită, domnule.
Sunt femeie!
Vezi? Cineva tocmai ți-a furat lucrurile!
Ce?!
Oh, păi...
Moț de șosete!
Vrei să spui hoț de poșete!
Huh? Who's this idiot?
He can't catch up on foot...
Holy shit, he's fast!
Oh, anti-gravity shoes!
Take this!
Antimat... Thigh Bomber!
Say what?!
Argh!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Antimat
Thigh Bomber
!!
Oh, no, wait!
I was trying to say Ultimate Divebomber.
Dang, why did I have to come up with such a tongue-twister of a name...
Are you okay?
Here's your bag.
You got it back for me? Thank you so much!
Antimat Thigh Bomber!
That wasn't my name!
Who'd name their kid "Thigh," anyway?
Heck, who launches an attack while screaming his own name?
Thank you so very much!
Seriously...
Oh, patrol bots!
Spaceport security sure is quick.
This guy's a purse-snatcher.
I guess I kinda knocked him out by accident.
You are under arrest for assault.
Huh?
Wha?
Catch, and...
Go!
One, two! One, two!
Hey! You got the wrong guy!
Wait, please!
Passengers boarding AQF flight 318 to Ikemir...
Your flight will begin boarding at noon.
Oh, are you going on the camping trip, too?
What? Um, I mean...
I'm sorry.
What?! Sorry for what?!
Hey there. Are you lost?
No, I'm not lost.
Oh. That's good. This is where...
What are you doing?
Calculating the trajectory from here to Planet McPa.
Quitterie.
But why, though?
Just for fun.
Oh, it's you.
Stop hovering. What do you want?
It's... nothing.
Can we go already?
Just wait a bit longer. I'll explain when everyone's here.
You know we're past schedule, right?
Fashionably late from the very beginning? Must be nice.
Ugh.
How rude, right?
I'm sorry.
Seriously, why?!
I'm sorry!
I'm late!
Finally showed up, huh?
No need for that. You are?
Um, a hearse catcher got me, and a guy saved me,
but he got one-two one-two'ed, and...
It was just a huge guess!
Catch a breath and make some sense, please!
At least give me your name and class!
Okay!
Aries Spring, Class 2-B!
I love poetry, and my special skill is that I never forget people I meet.
My personality is, uh...
Oh, people say I can't read the room.
I just can't understand why!
I said name and class, not life story!
That's basic room reading!
What's her deal?
She's an odd girl.
Takes one to know one.
So, back on track.
This is the day you've been waiting for.
Space Camp for team B-5 at Caird High.
We teachers will deliver you to Planet McPa, then leave immediately after.
The goal of the Planet Camp is to spend five days on site,
eight students only.
The team was assembled randomly.
Most of you are surely meeting for the first time.
Deepen your bonds, feel the vastness of space,
and have a great experience.
Also...
This is Funicia Rafaeli, Quitterie's sister.
She will be joining you on this camp.
Each team is assigned a special task.
In your case, that task is bringing along a ten-year-old.
So we asked Quitterie to bring her sister.
Come on, say hi.
I'm Funicia. I'm ten years old!
I'm sure I'll be a bother to you all, but...
Are you sure it's okay to take this kid along?
I'm really uncomfortable around kids, y'know?
I... I'll be...
I'll be dragging you around by your skinny little arms until ya puke if you don't shut up, you brat!
Funicia!
That was Beego, not me.
Impressive.
It's a puppet that automatically converts thoughts into a cartoon character's voice.
Anyway, so this team will have one more member than usual.
Hey, Mom!
You mean Sir!
Sir, you said we'd have one more,
but we have the normal eight right now.
Yes, we're still missing one.
If he doesn't make it in time,
we'll just leave him behind.
Whew, that was close!
Getting left behind for being late? Not cool at all.
.......................................
Tadah!
One, two! One, two!
.......................................
Tadah!
You're already uncool!
.......................................
Tadah!
So who are you? Are you part of the group?
I was finally able to clear everything up.
Kanata Hoshijima. I'm your captain!
Follow me, everyone!
Let's head out to Planet McPa!
Wait, I thought we were supposed choose a captain by vote.
Yeah, so I thought I might declare my candidacy early.
What's wrong with this guy?
He should be sorry, not bossy!
What a first impression.
I doubt anyone's gonna be voting for you.
What? For real?
Retreat, retreat...
Yer gettin' real worked up over a little family vacation, fella.
But I guess kids get excited about this kinda stuff.
Why the hell does this puppet sound like an old geezer?
Caird High Space Ship
_
Ready_
Caird High Space Ship
Ready for_
Ready for depar
Ready for departure
That pink and black suit is from SMB, right?
Same as Funi's!
Yep!
I don't have siblings, so I'm jealous of sisters who are close.
Can't say it's that great.
Funi, I love your little skirt!
Yunhua, your suit is by Hyperion!
Same as mine!
Yes.
Whoa... Awesome!
He's pretty interesting.
His declaration to run, I mean.
Is captain that attractive a position?
It's a big responsibility.
Out of my way.
They'd be the one who has to get all of us to agree on things.
Sorry.
What are you talking about?
Who should be captain.
Yes! Me! I volunteer!
Calm down. That's why you didn't get chosen.
Past tense? How?
Excuse me.
Oh, sorry.
It's pretty much settled, yeah?
Who knows where you'd lead us off to if you became captain.
What?!
Wandering off on an adventure sounds like fun!
You mean getting lost.
Okay, we're taking off. Fasten your seatbelts.
I'm ready.
Did something happen?
How should I know?
I recently transferred to this school.
No wonder you seemed unfamiliar.
Yep! It's only been about a month.
I hope we can be great friends, Quitterie!
I'm only here for the class credit.
Not to play nicey-nice with any of you.
I...
I want to be friends with everyone.
She didn't listen to a single word I said, did she?
I'm so excited for this camp!
Increase output to Ether engines.
Deploy Cleaving Field.
Transition to acceleration-expansion phase. Begin Cleaving.
We've entered faster-than-light travel.
You can deactivate your helmets and relax.
Wow, it's stuffy in here. Can I open the windows?
Four hours is a lot. Isn't there a TV or something?
Is there a shower on this ship?
I can't relax without changing into my bathrobe.
I said relax, not lose all control!
I've finally come this far...
Teacher.
Teacher, I'm not planning on going to space anymore.
Track and field is is what I'm best at. I want to focus on it.
Is it your dad?
Yeah...
A life dedicated to sports can be as fulfilling as any other.
But you're much too young to lock in what's best for you based on what you're good at.
Then how do I know what to do?
You follow what you like, of course.
Do you really think life is that easy?
I really do.
You can reach the skies, and beyond.
Really?
Yes, and my purpose is to help you do just that.
Wow...
Excuse me!
Thank you for helping me at the space port!
Hey, Aries Spring.
Didn't know you were in the same group!
Oh wow, you learned my name already!
Thank you very much!
Uh... Kanata...
Something something Bomber!
Hey, I remembered your name!
I had my wallet in this bag. I can't thank you enough.
As a token of my gratitude...
Nah, don't mention it.
Would you like a frozen tangerine?
Are you my grandma?!
I was really impressed
that you volunteered to become champion.
Er, I think you mean captain.
Why did you, though?
I want to be an explorer someday. A space explorer!
I want to own a ship and go to planets no one's seen before.
I thought being captain here would be a great first step.
Whoa.
That's amazing! You have such a clear dream of what you want to do already.
It was actually the dream of someone I owe a lot to.
He passed away in an accident a while back.
I don't know if I can say I'm carrying on his wishes,
but that was the trigger for me choosing my dream.
That's so moving! I'm sure you'll achieve it!
Whoa, th-thanks... Wow, you're passionate...
By the way, would you like some barley tea?
Are you sure you're not my grandma?!
_
Planet McPa
Ca_
Camp_
Camp de
Camp dest
Camp destin
Camp destinati
Camp destination
Atmosphere check.
Content, pressure, both okay.
Students.
We've arrived at Planet McPa!
Hooray!
Take your belongings and enter the airlock.
Once everyone's off the ship, we'll be leaving you and heading home.
We'll be back for you in five days.
This is McPa...
It didn't look nearly this amazing from the ship!
Look at the clouds.
Those are clouds? They look like lakes.
We're really on a different planet...
Okay then.
Let's get to the lodge, change out of these suits, and explore!
Hey! Why are you bossing us around?
Don't wander off on your own, now.
There's no telling what's out here.
Was that an explosion?!
Huh? What?
Does the ground explode on this planet?!
Don't worry, that's just his anti-gravity unit.
It must have been damaged by the Ultimate Divebomb...
What's that?
Let's leave the idiot here and get to the lodge.
Hey, don't leave your captain behind.
Who said you're captain?
Hey guys, what is that?
What the heck?
I've never seen anything like it.
It's coming closer.
Be careful, everyone!
Huh, this is cool.
Hey, wait...
Hey you, stop!
What, are you scared?
We're on a foreign planet, sure,
but this place is practically a nature park.
Obviously this is just theatrics.
Everyone, run!
If you've disabled your helmets, get them back on!
W-W-Wait...
What's going on?
You're going to be all right.
I'm pulling you up.
Teacher! I can help!
Okay, grab the other arm!
Teacher! Hold on!
I'll get a rope!
Get away from the ledge, it's too dangerous!
Don't worry about me. Focus on saving yourselves!
Help is coming. You have to survive until then.
When things seem hopeless...
Act tough!
What?! Why am I in space?!
Is that...
Can anyone hear me?
Everyone else is...
Guys, can you hear me?
Are your comms working?
Working fine here!
What the heck is going on?!
What are we doing in space?!
It's that sphere.
It sucked us in and spat us out here.
This is a full-blown emergency.
Who has the communicator to the school?
I did, but I think I dropped it.
Then it's lost. Is there anywhere we can evacuate to?
Huh?
Is that a ship over there?
What?!
Do you think there might be someone there?
Everyone sees the ship, right? Let's regroup there!
Use your thrusters.
They don't have much fuel, but there should be enough to reach the ship.
Were you looking for this?
Guys, try to recover luggage if you see any nearby.
What's going on?
Why is this happening?
No response from the inside.
It must be abandoned.
The power's online.
Once everyone's inside, close the airlock!
Do you see the gravity controls?
I just activated them.
Hey, what's going on? What is this?!
Brace yourselves, gravity incoming!
Looks like a locker room over there.
Let's gather there for now.
What is going on?!
What was that ball?!
Calm down, Quitterie.
First, let's check if we're all safe.
Are all nine of us here?
Is anyone injured?
Hey...
We're missing one.
Who?
Who are we missing?!
Is that her?
I see her! That's...
Aries!
Her thrusters must be disabled!
Looks like her comms are down too.
We have to go save her!
She's too far. If you run out of fuel,
you won't be able to come back.
But...
It's hopeless then!
What are we gonna do?!
Shut up! Less shouting, more thinking!
When things seem hopeless...
Act tough!
I'll go.
If there's one word I hate more than anything else,
it's "hopeless."
Is it secure?
Yeah.
You should be able to make the one-way trip.
We'll pull you back with the wire.
I'm going.
How is he?
A little off to the right.
Kanata, you're off!
Really? Which way?
Right! Oh wait, she's moving too, so...
Uh... Left? West?
Make up your mind!
Kanata, conserve your thruster fuel. Minimize your bursts!
One-point-five second burst, seven o'clock.
Once you're on the trajectory,
let inertia take you there.
You got it!
You're on the way.
Hold on...
Aries!
There's no one here.
I'm scared.
Being all alone is terrifying!
Kanata!
Hey there! Dizzy enough yet?
There's not enough wire!
Crap!
Get to space,
Kanata!
If the rope won't reach her...
What is he doing?
I'll go alone!
Here... we... go.
Okay, this is pretty terrifying.
Darkness all around.
I could easily drown in the fear.
Nowhere to go but forward.
Can you see me now, Teacher?
Kanata! Kanata!
Way to hang in there, Aries!
Hold on, don't let go.
Yeah, you're saying "thank you," right?
Okay, time for the hard part...
Can they come back?
The wire's far out of reach now,
but there should be enough fuel left to drift back here with inertia.
Just enough.
Now, as long as I stay on course...
No, they won't.
Their trajectory is off, five degrees downwards.
They're going to fly past us.
What should we do?!
He doesn't have any more thruster fuel...
Then there's nothing we can do.
I want to be friends with everyone.
I know!
Hey!
Lend me a hand!
Am I out of reach again?
Kanata, look!
Dude, are you—
Now we're even.
Huh?
Kanata!
Welcome home, friend.
That was crazy dangerous!
Sorry!
Are you saying something?
I was so scared, but now that I have a hand to hold on to,
space suddenly looks very beautiful to me.
That's what I said.
Thank you so much!
S'okay, really.
It's not your fault that your suit was broken.
You really can't be left alone, can you?
I owe you all my life.
Oh, stop it. It's not like we took a stupid risk like Kanata did.
Anyway, it's too bad the comms are broken on this ship.
We have to get in touch with the school ASAP.
They should notice when we miss our first check-in.
What? So we have to sit and wait for help?
McPa is only nine light years from home.
It'll only take them four hours.
Well, at least we're alive, right?
Don't be so sure that help is coming.
Look at that planet. I just surveyed it.
It's a lifeless, ice-covered planet.
It's not McPa.
We're not over McPa?!
Currently, this ship is...
5,012 light years away.
F-Five thousand twelve light years?!
I don't understand how that's possible.
But given how far we are,
the chance of a rescue is close to none.
Space camp log, Aries Spring, day one.
We, team B5 of Caird High Planet Camp,
have been washed up on the far shores of space.
Acting tough is getting really hard now...
W-What's going on?
What do you mean, 5,012 light years?!
I don't understand how it happened.
That sphere engulfed us and spat us out 5,000 light years into deep space.
Hey, so can we go back in the ball and go back to where we were?
You could be right!
So where is that handy little ball, then?
Think it's hiding in the bathroom or something?
What the hell's your problem, Professor Asshole?
Easy, easy.
He does have a point, though. The ball isn't here,
and we don't even know how to find it.
You might be right about that.
Then what are we supposed to do?
Um...
I was thinking... Maybe this is like a test of some sort?
A test?
Think about it. It's just too weird!
Five thousand light years in an instant?
And we just happen to appear next to a ship? Yeah, right!
Maybe the ship's computers are lying and we're actually still over McPa.
I bet they're watching us to see how we tackle the situation!
T-That's it!
That sounds like the best explanation!
Yeah, it's all staged!
You might be right!
Our helmets...
Kanata told us to put our helmets on, remember?
But...
...if we hadn't, we would have died instantly.
I don't think the school would do something so dangerous.
You might be right about that.
How many times are you going to say "You might be right"?!
We found ourselves a ship, sure, but it might as well be a coffin if there's no way to fly it.
Hey, Zack! You have a spaceship license, don't you?
Huh? As a high school student? Seriously?
That's right.
You actually do? Then why didn't you say something?!
I didn't want to.
What's his deal?!
Is he famous?
You didn't know?
He's Zack Walker, the über-genius prodigy with 200 IQ.
No, we didn't know. And why are you the one bragging?
The ship is old, but it can fly using propellant gathered from space outside.
So we can get home!
All right!
Everyone, calm down.
If we have to travel 5,000 light years,
it would take at least three months even at the fastest FTL setting.
Even with all of our baggage put together, we only have enough food and water for three days of travel.
What if we lighten the load of the ship?
Can we disable a limiter and boost the engines?
I calculated all of that already.
Even with full tanks, the ship can only carry 20 days' worth of water.
This ship just isn't capable of traveling 5,000 light years.
Way to milk your moment in the limelight.
Just say it a little simpler. It's hopeless.
Tell us straight up that your big brain can't think of a
solution, so all that's left is for us is to rot here and die.
Whoa!
Fighting won't help.
Everyone, calm down and listen!
The more you get scared, the more you panic!
It's number three on my list of survival tips.
What's he saying?
You're just stating the obvious.
Just listen to me for a bit. I want to tell a story.
Why should we listen to you?
When I was in middle school, I went on a mountain climbing trip.
We got lost there, just five students.
Just students? What about the teacher?
An unexpected storm, a broken communicator, a landslide...
A bunch of accidents happened at once, and a student got into a panic and slipped.
Our teacher went to save him and fell down a ledge.
He lost his life.
The rest of us, just kids, survived for seven days until help arrived.
It was a miracle that none of us died.
I've heard of that—the Surugi Middle School Incident.
You were part of it?
We almost gave up more than once.
But everyone in the group cheered each other up.
I'm sure I would have died without them.
We have to stick together.
If we're surrounded by darkness,
we have to hold on to each other's hands.
I totally get it!
When I thought it was all over out there,
you all held hands to save me.
But right now, we're all disconnected.
We don't even know each other's names.
That's not right!
So, let's start things over and...
Quitterie. Quitterie Rafaeli.
Zack Walker. I'm studying to become a researcher.
Luca here. I'm good at making stuff.
Trying to get into an art school.
Charce Lacroix. I guess I'm good at biology.
What about you?
Introduce yourself.
I'm Yunhua.
I'm not good at anything, but...
I... I'm sorry.
You know...
There's nothing to be sorry about.
He's good-looking, but his rhythm is weird!
Come, my dear.
How is his face shining?!
One day, you'll get your turn to shine.
Even his words are dazzling!
I'm Funicia Rafaeli, the little sister.
I'm Ulgar.
Pleasure to meetcha!
What is this?!
I'm Beego, sonny.
Don't get all flustered. It's just hand-holding!
His first close encounter with something alien.
I know!
Maybe if we make connections, we can make it!
What do you mean?
I think I get it!
Even if we can't do it alone, together, we could reach out.
So we can all be stars!
W-Where is she going with this?!
Stars... You mean planets?
Yes!
Huh? What?
If there's a planet within three days of here with food and water...
I can enter the conditions into this list of planets I brought along.
I found one.
Planet Vilavurs.
Less than three days from here.
If we go to that planet and stock up on food and water,
we can fly for 20 more days.
I see!
Then, if we can find another planet with food and water...
Wait, seriously? Is this possible?
And we keep connecting planets that are 20 days apart or less...
Just how many planets are we gonna have to visit?
That's fine.
We can make progress, little by little.
I got it.
There's just one route, spanning five planets.
It's a miracle! There really is a way home!
Good job, Zack!
Do you really think it'll actually work?
I'd say 50/50.
But it's either that or death.
If there's a way, let's get right on it.
Survival tip number one:
going forward results in progress!
Stating the obvious again!
Are you stupid or something?
Let's get this ship moving.
Yeah!
Is everyone seated? Strap in, okay?
Please remain seated while the sign is on.
We get it, so you sit, too.
On the captain's seat.
Huh?
I suppose we'll need a leader if we want to stay together.
Yes. And he volunteered, too.
I agree!
Yes!
You betcha.
Fine by me, I guess.
Oh, but I'm not ready to be captain!
Why the sudden change?!
There aren't any more chairs. Just sit.
Huh? Uh, okay.
Okay, let's go.
Set course. First planet, Vila—
Does this ship have a name?
Don't cut me off!
A name, a name...
Who cares what...
What's that? Written on that plate.
Per Aspera Ad Astra.
What's that?
Aspera means hardship. Astra means star.
Overcome hardships to reach your goal.
That's nice. A lot better than Kanata's dumb survival tips.
What?!
So it's an old word for "star"?
Works for me. The ship's name is the Astra!
Set course for the first planet, Vilavurs.
Activate faster-than-light engines!
itsumo no hoshizora
The same starry sky I see every night
itsuka wa bokura ni mo todoku no kana
Will I, too, reach it one day?
matataku kiseki yubi de nazoreba
As my finger traces a glowing miracle,
kuyashisa ga nijinda
A drop of frustration falls on it
sore wa takasugiru keshiki no mukougawa de
My tears fall because I know that there's a world waiting for us beyond the horizon
machiwabita sekai ga aru to shitteiru namida
Beyond the awe and terror of standing on this lonely summit
hitori dewa kanawanai yume dakara
Though I could never realize this dream by myself,
bokura ga koko ni iru imi wo shinjirareru yuuki de
We just need the courage to believe that there's a reason we're here
haruka kimi he tadoritsuketara
As we manage to reach you, far though you may be,
natsukashii kanata no koe ga kikoeru yo
We'll hear the familiar voice that lay across the sea of stars
ASTRAL PRESENTS