Ce?!
You still can't find La Folia
or any of the others?
I'm very sorry.
Our surveillance cameras were damaged
beyond repair in last night's attack.
Akatsuki Kojou, you idiot.
If anything happens to Yukina,
I'll make you pay.
Um, what's this all about?
Aiba-san...
Kojou and the others were abducted?!
The embassy has received a notice from someone
claiming responsibility for the abduction!
For the release of the princess,
they demand the release of eleven
political prisoners being held in Aldeigia.
Damn it!
All the prisoners on this list are serving
life sentences for extreme felonies!
Are you going to accept their demands?
La Folia-chan will be just fine.
She knows very well what we
would do in this situation,
and what she must do.
You're right.
Aldeigia will not cave to terrorists!
We have always lived by that policy,
and we always will!
But then, Kojou and the others will—
Don't worry.
Aldeigia, as a kingdom of magic,
will spare no effort
in saving La Folia and all the others.
Per our arrangement,
I sent the notice and the demand
for the political prisoners.
Of course, knowing the country
we're dealing with,
it's unlikely they'll accept that demand.
Probably not.
But it will cause unrest and buy us time.
You people are so rock-solid
in your precautions.
Does growing up in a cold country
freeze your thought processes stiff, too?
We value certainty, that's all.
I hope you are aware, Trine Halden,
that we expect you to be worth
the reward we're paying you.
No need to worry about that.
I managed to get my hands
on a tool I wasn't expecting.
On the pride of the Free Terrorists,
I promise you that I will
fulfill your request...
and kill that man.
Listen to me.
Our Progenitor desires the continuation
of the cease-fire agreement.
Don't make the mistake of creating
such a ruckus that you ruin this.
And what if they were
to make a move on us first?
In that case, you would
have no other choice.
Feel free to crush them.
I've finished this foot.
It looks great, Kojou.
Now, this one's next.
With pleasure.
Keep it down, little girl.
You're just an extra
that came along with La Folia.
If you can't be quiet,
I won't hesitate to kill you.
Ah...
Little girl, you're jealous, aren't you?
You're in love with Kojou.
It's too noisy out here.
Let's finish this in bed.
Of course.
I can't walk until my nails are dry.
Carry me, Kojou.
With pleasure, my lady.
The signing ceremony between Aldeigia
and the Warlord's Empire
is scheduled to take place this afternoon
on Itogami Island's newly built megafloat...
The two nations clashed several
times in the 20th century,
but ever since the peace accord was signed,
the military and financial
resources they had been using
to fight each other have been
directed elsewhere.
Both nations have made
remarkable progress since.
The Aldeigia royal family is known
for its beautiful women.
The princess and queen are both
renowned as global fashion leaders.
One wonders what sort
of dresses they will don today.
How exciting!
Representing the Warlord's Empire
is Imperial Diet Chairman Aladar.
He is accompanied by...
I heard Kojou got roped
into some trouble again.
Yeah. I'm heading back to the school
to find out as much as I can.
Let me know when you find something.
Well, this pretty much guarantees
something will happen during the ceremony...
Hey, you!
This area is off-limits!
Show us your ID!
You don't need to know my name!
Light. Too light.
Feel the weight of a fist
that has been cursed by the gods.
You—
Who wants to be the next
one to taste my fist?
What did you do to Senpai?!
Despite how he looks, he's a Progenitor.
Hypnotic magic or control magic
of any kind shouldn't work on him!
That's a trade secret.
Remember this well, understand?
I could order Kojou to kill both of you
or even himself right now.
That means all three of you
are holding each other hostage.
If any of the three
of you steps out of line,
someone among you will die.
Okay, time to move.
Listen, Mogwai. Look for Kojou.
Focus on places that are relevant
to the Kingdom of Aldeigia.
Sheesh, that's gonna be a pain...
Or maybe not. Just happened
to pick up a disturbance.
Where?
The airport.
That brand new armored airship,
Bifröst, just put out a mayday call.
Conquest complete.
Good work, Kojou.
Is this why you kidnapped me?
Starting up the main engine
of a royal family airship
requires a royal family member's
biometric authentication.
If you know that,
I'd appreciate it if you'd
just start up the ship now.
What is it you hope to do?
We're going to crash
the signing ceremony with this ship
and kill Lord Ardeal.
What?!
Why didn't you say that sooner?
If I had known, I would've helped you
without being kidnapped!
La Folia-san?!
I've wanted to kill
Lord Ardeal for a long time.
Don't you get it?
An Aldeigia airship is going to
kill a Warlord's Empire noble!
Do you realize what—
The peace agreement would be voided,
and war would break out.
But that's what you people
of the North Sea Empire want, isn't it?
It appears I was right.
Please, do as you like.
If we can take advantage of the chaos
to eliminate Lord Ardeal,
I'll consider it a windfall.
Of course, I'm the one
who'll be sending the ship.
Main engine online.
We have no further use for you two.
Kojou, throw them both into the cabin.
Understood.
Let's go.
Why do you keep letting
this woman order you around?!
This could end in a war!
Quit your yapping, little girl.
I told you, Kojou is mine.
Aren't you?
Yes, my lady.
Senpai, you jerk!
Damn it! I'm too late!
This is Heimdal.
Bifröst just took off!
Alert the Island Guard
and ceremony security.
I'm sorry to ask this of you
on such short notice, Kanon-chan.
No, I'm very happy that I could be of use.
Well, ready to go, La Folia-chan?
Yes, Mother.
Why did you start up the ship?
Are you really going to tell me
you don't care if there's a war?
That was just a joke, of course...
excluding the part about
wanting to kill Lord Ardeal.
But that's sure to lead to war!
I'll stop it.
How?
Yukina, don't you feel a bit cold?
What?
That must be it.
Prepare anti-aircraft artillery!
It's the Island Guard.
Did you finish rewriting that program?
Yes, sir!
Good. Let them down!
What is that?
Bergelmir?!
The magic weapons of Aldeigia's military!
Fire the missiles!
We don't have time to adjust the aim!
The Island Guard will be stuck
here protecting the island.
So the ceremony venue...
I, War Dancer of the High God,
as a dancer of the Lion, beseech thee!
Enku of the Aurora, Qilin of radiant light,
thou who doth rule thunder and the heavens,
come clad in raging fire
to pierce Hell's monstrous demons!
There are so many.
If this keeps up...
Execute Rhododactylos.
What are those things?
Military magic weapons.
State of the art, too.
They're gonna be a tough match.
But the bigger problem is Bifröst.
It's cruising straight toward
the ceremony venue, unchecked.
Seriously... why did this have to happen?
Whatcha doing?
Taking over Bifröst's systems!
Yeah? But that's a warship's
firewall you're up against.
Think you can do it?
Whether I can or not, I'm going to!
Next to speak for the Warlord's Empire,
representing the Lost Warlord,
is Imperial Diet Chairman Veres Aladar.
Prepare to drop Aurgelmir!
You've got less than three minutes
before they get there.
This really is tough...
If I can just find a starting point,
no matter how small...
How about this, then?
Is this... the magic weapon from before?
Bingo!
If you knew about this, you should've
told me sooner, you hunk of junk!
Urgență
There's been an explosion on board!
It must've been those little girls.
Honestly, they're such scamps.
I can't believe you hid
explosives in your extensions!
But still, why did you
have to make our room so hot?
I'm soaked with sweat now!
Really? That must have been awful.
That's all you can say?
Actually, I don't see
any sweat on you at all.
I was keeping myself cool
with cooling magic the whole time.
Huh?!
That's as far as you go, little girls.
If you'd behaved, I would've come up
with some other way to use you.
Too bad.
Kill them, Kojou.
Yes, my lady.
Senpai...
What is this?!
Hey!
This is...
We're being hacked from outside!
Got the piloting system!
I'm not letting you get any farther!
Steering is down!
What about Aurgelmir?!
The hatch won't open!
Well, fire control is still online, right?!
Which means...
Launching!
A cruise missile...
What a beautiful gun salute.
I wish for nothing but further prosperity
and peace for both of our countries.
It blew itself up?!
The fire control system was...
Just in time.
What a shame.
What the hell are you doing?!
Someone took control of Bifröst from us!
In that case...
Kojou!
Yes, my lady?
It would've been best to do this
with one of Aldeigia's weapons,
but now there's no choice.
Burn the ceremony venue
to the ground with your Familiar!
Yes, my lady.
I won't let you!
Senpai!
Senpai?
Just like always, Himeragi...
You smell so good.
Senpai...
Kojou... why?
Give up now. Kojou won't
listen to you anymore.
You're a therianthrope...
One of the civet family,
if I'm not mistaken.
I've heard before that
there are some therianthropes
that can use pheromones
to bewitch other people, even vampires.
That's right.
But no one has ever been able to
escape my pheromones before.
How did he...
It's quite simple.
I made sure Yukina got good
and sweaty before coming here.
Between the scent of a youthful
middle school girl's sweat
and an old lady's fake,
perfumed body odor...
It's no challenge to figure out
which would be more alluring.
Who are you calling an old lady?!
Oh! How rude of me!
You're not an old lady. You're an old hag.
You little bitch!
It can't be...
Looks like the guys down below
knew what they needed to do!
I don't care!
Break through its armor, Aurgelmir!
Look out!
You and this ship,
as well as the ceremony venue...
I'm going to crush all of it!
Senpai...
Himeragi...
Now, let's just see how long you can keep
that calm look on your face!
Pulsation!
Damn you, little girl!
Sword Shaman!
Got a gift for you from the War Dancer.
Some nerve, using me
as her delivery service...
I'll round up the terrorists.
You can handle things here,
right, Akatsuki Kojou?
Yeah.
Hey, terrorist chick...
You've been using me
as your toy long enough.
From now on,
this is my fight!
No, Senpai.
This is our fight!
Shut up!
I, Akatsuki Kojou, successor to
the blood of Kaleid Blood,
now release your constraints.
Come, fifth Familiar,
Regulus Aurum!
I, Sword Shaman of the High God,
as a priestess of the Lion, beseech thee...
Dawn light of exorcism, spirit wolf of snowy mist...
Grant me the divine might of thy steel,
that I may smite a hundred evil spirits!
We did it, Senpai!
Yeah.
But...
I guess we might have overdone it a bit.
Huh?
Wha?!
Gimme a break!
Thank you, Kojou.
I've truly enjoyed my stay here.
Oh, yeah? Glad to hear that.
Kanon-chan, I hope you'll
come visit us in Aldeigia next.
Sure!
I'm so happy for you, Kanon-chan.
It's kind of a shame that this all ended
while I was sleeping late, though...
Kojou-san, please do give some
thought to marrying La Folia.
If you do, we'll forget that the damage
to Bifröst ever happened.
Listen up, you!
Don't get cocky just
because you defeated Aurgelmir!
It was the weakest
of Aldeigia's magic weapons!
We've still got Loki, Thor,
and our latest weapon, Odin!
Yes, yes. Time to go now, dear.
Our latest weapon, Odin, I say!
Okay.
Sheesh...
They're finally heading home.
What's wrong, Himeragi?
S-Senpai, you don't remember what happened
when you were being controlled
by that "Trine" woman, do you?
Isn't that what I told you?
I mean... you know...
I kinda remember defeating Aurgelmir,
but I have no memory
of anything before that.
I hope so... for both our sakes.
Huh? Both of us?
I don't know about me,
but you're fine, right?
So you do remember!
I mean, I can't help it!
I'm the one who was humiliated over being forced
to act like some eighth-grade edgelord!
You have nothing to be embarra—
Hey! What the hell?! That hurts!
You're such an indecent person, Senpai!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
How could you let her order you around?!
What did you do when you were
in that bedroom with her?!
And...
When you hugged me while I was all sweaty
and said with a straight face
that I smelled good... I...
Huh?
Ugh! What are you trying to make me say?!
You jerk!