De ce este Laminitus în camera mea?
Și mai ales în acea costumație!
Mi-ar plăcea să rămâi aici în orașul Turnul de Zircon pentru multă vreme.
Nu prea pot face asta din moment ce...
Lumachina mi-a cerut deja ajutorul.
I don't know if the Church can protect people
from the resurrected Demon Lord so long as
it's in the hands of those
indulging in selfish desires.
Ce plănuiești să faci?
Ei bine, cred că mă voi întoarce în capitala regală.
Ai uitat că sunt oameni care vor să te omoare?
Chiar așa de mult vrei să mori?
Diablo!
Ajută-mă, te rog!
Bănuiesc că nu am de ales decât să merg cu ea.
Acum, cum îi voi explica asta lui Laminitus într-o manieră potrivită unui Lord Demon?
Hmpf. Inamicul meu se află în capitala regală.
Dacă intenționezi să intervii, atunci te voi...
Hei, stai!
Nu trebuie să te grăbești acolo chiar acum, nu?
Ți-am pregătit un spectacol numai bun pentru un oaspete, știi.
Asta este ideea ei de spectacol?!
Este așa de tare, Diablo.
Da, așa este! Pentru că sunt coarnele mele!
Ești așa de puternic, Diablo.
D-Doar am nivelul 150...
Cred că ne putem simți amândoi bine.
Îmi place să fiu cea mai bună în tot ce fac.
Nu ai mai simțit niciodată așa ceva.
Despre ce vorbește?!
Mă voi asigura că nu vrei să pleci de lângă mine.
Trebuie să fug chiar acum!
Este o creatură demonică la fereastră!
Ce?
Diablo?
Hei!
Nu te voi lăsa să scapi data viitoare,
Diablo.
Episodul 7: Micuțul Lord Demon
Putem vedea Faltra!
Ne-am întors în sfârșit.
Sper că sunt bine Klem și Edelgard.
I-am cerut lui Mei să aibă grijă de ele, deci sunt bine fără îndoială.
Ne vom îndrepta spre capitala regală imediat cum e toată lumea gata, nu?
Da.
Iar pentru asta, vom avea nevoie mai întâi de o caleașcă.
Voi face aranjamentele pentru asta.
Oh, voi merge cu tine!
Ce s-a întâmplat?
Mi-ar plăcea să vizitez biserica din acest oraș.
Ce? Chiar este în regulă?
Ești ținta cardinalilor care controlează Biserica.
Chiar și preotul de aici ți-ar putea fi inamic.
Dar s-a dus o bătălie contra creaturilor demonice aici în Faltra și mulți oameni...
Vreau să mă rog pentru sufletele lor.
În acest caz...
Te voi conduce eu acolo!
Îmi voi face griji dacă Shera va fi singura ta gardă.
Ce?!
În acest caz!
Dacă o femeie are nevoie de protecție, atunci puteți conta pe mine!
Numele meu este Emile Bichelberger!
Eu sunt aliatul tuturor femeilor!
Și aliatul aliaților femeilor!
Stăpâne, acest om este dubios.
Cine este acest tip?
Ei bine, chiar pare dubios.
M-ai putea proteja tu?
Mă voi baza pe tine.
Sunt fericit că ai încredere în mine.
Te voi proteja negreșit!
Hei!
Nu ar trebui să accepți o misiune în timp ce îndeplinești deja alta!
Dar, lider al breslei...
Este vorba de protejarea unei femei. Asta are cea mai înaltă prioritate!
Doamne... Ești în mijlocul unui antrenament de sabie, știi?
Sylvie, nu ne-am văzut de mult timp.
Ne-am întors!
Bine ați revenit, Rem, Shera, Diablo!
Văd că acum ai și mai multe femei prin preajmă.
Există un motiv bun pentru asta.
Atunci, se pare că nu s-au schimbat prea multe.
Oh, apropo, Klem este la brutăria Peter din sudul districtului.
Brutărie?
S-a dus acolo ca să cumpere biscuiți sau ceva?
Nu.
Se pare că Edelgard a început să lucreze acolo cu jumătate de normă.
O creatură demonică lucrează cu jumătate de normă la o brutărie?
Asta e acea brutărie?
Da.
C-Ce naiba...
este acest loc dubios?!
Bine...
Bine ai revenit,
Lordule Demon!
Edelgard, chiar lucrezi aici cu jumătate de normă?
Voi câștiga bani ca să pot plăti pentru biscuiții Lordului Demon.
Nu prea are o viață ușoară.
Oh, Diablo!
Bine ai revenit, Lordule Demon! Miau, miau!
Tu ești Mei, fata de la han.
Ce s-a întâmplat cu hanul Pacea Minții?
We haven't been getting many guests lately.
With the rumors about the Demon Lord's
resurrection, fewer people are traveling west.
She has it rough, too.
Oh, this is a Fallen café, nya.
Relax and enjoy yourself, nya!
A Fallen café?
I get it. That would keep
Edelgard from standing out.
Hey, now, stop playing around.
Boss...
We're a normal bakery, you know...
But it's all gone crazy since
we hired Edelgard-chan.
They're so good!
Wait, Klem, that's where you were?
Owner, bring out more biscuits!
Jeez...
This one's been eating
biscuits since this morning.
Eat some bread now and then, too.
The Demon Lord's orders are absolute.
Refusing them warrants death.
I'll go bake some biscuits!
Hang in there, owner!
World peace rests on this shop's biscuits!
I see you've returned safely, Diablo.
I'm still traveling. We're heading
to the royal capital next.
Did you butt into some trouble again?
Something like that.
Watching you reminds me of the Hero.
That's not funny.
I'm the Demon Lord.
Though in this store, I just look
like a customer who's into the act.
So what are you going to
the royal capital for?
Is a Demon Lord like you going to side
with that Human who reeks of God?
Hmph.
I'm just going there to
crush some annoying pests.
That's exactly what makes
you sound like the Hero.
Huh?
Well, just try to be careful.
There's an odd presence in the east.
It's not a Demon Lord,
but it's some kind of great power.
Oh?
I'm interested in hearing about that.
Long time no see, Diablo-san.
Celestine Baudelaire?!
What are you doing in a place like this?
Oh, you know I can't leave this city.
So what's wrong with having a little tea?
Yeah, but should the person responsible for
the barrier that keeps monsters out of Faltra
The biscuits here are delicious!
be visiting a café where
the Demon Lord's present?
My, perhaps I should try some, then.
Oh, actually... I guess it's because
I asked her to watch over Klem when we left.
Klem-chan and I are café buddies.
We are!
How peaceful.
Hey, hey!
Who gave you permission to run a shop here?!
You don't think the Measmos
family means business?!
H-Heavens, no!
Huh?!
Ugh, what's going on now?
I don't want to get involved.
Hey, today's your lucky day.
We'll sell you this Pig Statue
of Profitable Business
that the Mage's Association
created for just 10,000 friths!
That's so much money!
You know you're happy about it!
Come on, buy it!
I don't recall us ever making
something in such poor taste.
Please, spare me!
You think we don't mean business, huh?!
What a problem.
Customers are precious.
But still...
You okay with not being able to do
business anymore? Huh, huh, huh?!
So they're finally showing
up around here, too...
Come on!
Oh, well...
Pay up, damn it!
Look! Now you're causing
trouble for your customers!
You idiot!
Infinity—
Don't kill him!
You imbecile.
You've angered a Demon Lord.
You should pay for your lack of knowledge
and character with a violent death.
My nose is bleeding!
Or so I would like to say,
but my master has ordered me not
to kill you, so I have to let you off.
W-We won't forget this!
Who was that?
A-A member of the Measmos family.
To be blunt, they're a
criminal organization, nya.
But they're smart about the way they operate,
so the local knights haven't
been able to arrest them.
Many people in the city have
suffered at their hands.
I have no choice now but to close up shop.
But then I won't be able
to eat any biscuits!
Damn that Measmos family!
I'll exterminate them!
Hey, now...
Oh? There was someone that strong there?
My apologies, boss!
Interesting.
Rust Burst!
That's a rather plain spell
for you to use, isn't it?
What happened to the one
you used against me?
Which one?
Apocalypse Abyss, was it?
If I used that one, this whole
area would become a wasteland!
I don't enjoy meaningless
commotion, that's all.
What's all this commotion?!
Which organization are you with?!
Do you realize this belongs
to the Measmos family?!
You dare defy...
the Demon Lord?
I'll kill you!
I'll kill all of them!
Wh-Who is this?!
This is bad!
If they kill anyone, even villains,
they won't be able to stay in the city!
Please wait.
You mustn't kill them.
Rose!
Death is too lenient for any
fool who dares to defy Master.
We must mince their limbs one by one
and teach them the full weight
of the sins they've committed.
That's even worse!
Quit screwing around!
Don't underestimate us!
If this keeps going, we're in trouble.
Explosion!
Was that magic?
Hmph.
So slow.
You three stand back.
Pardon me.
No fair!
I want to get them, too!
But if you do it, you'll kill them!
For crying out loud! Where is this Measmos guy?
What power!
My goodness...
I can't believe anyone's dumb
enough to storm the mansion.
Apparently, they don't know
that I've been hired.
Scarface is finally going to act!
Yeah!
He's the living legend who
defeated that Grand Orc in a duel!
He did it barehanded, too!
Are you Measmos?
If you can beat me,
I'll tell you where the boss is.
You're not Measmos?
I came here to see Measmos,
and I keep finding anything but!
It goes against my policy to
hit women and children,
but I'll make exceptions if it's for the job.
I won't hold back!
Yah.
How was that?!
Impressive.
You went overboard.
I thought we were getting him
to tell us where Measmos is?
I screwed up!
Hey!
If you value your life, then answer me.
You still haven't defeated the intruders?
Rest assured, Scarface will
take care of them soon enough.
I thought he was too expensive,
but he's reassuring to have at a time like this.
Hey! Is Measmos in here?!
I didn't think you'd make it this far.
Wh-Wh-What organization hired you?!
The Lord? The Commerce Guild?
How much did they pay you?! How much?!
This is their boss?
Tell me! Come on, tell me!
He's just some shabby old dude.
I-I know! Why don't you side with me?
I can pay you!
I'll pay double!
I don't care about the organizations
of the mortal races.
This is pure retaliation!
Wh-What are you talking about?
Yeah, I guess there's no way he'd understand.
Who'd expect a Demon Lord to attack
in retaliation for ruining her biscuits?
I'll slaughter you all!
You can regret angering the
Demon Lord in the afterlife!
Oh, no!
Wait!
Infinity Detonation!
Diablo! Why can I not kill this man, either?
If I said, "Even if they're a villain,
I don't want to see anyone die,"
it wouldn't be in character for a Demon Lord.
What do I do?
Oh, I know.
We'll mince his limbs...
And teach him the weight of his sins.
No!
Don't you dare!
In short, even if we kill him,
his evil deeds won't go away.
But wouldn't killing him be quicker?
It's no use!
My party members have nothing
but murder on their minds!
I know!
We have him apologize for his crimes!
Apologize?
Is that really enough?
The boss taught me to apologize
when I broke the dishes.
Ah, yes!
Exactly!
Have him atone by doing good deeds
equal to the crimes he's committed.
Oh, that idea kind of sounds better!
That's just like you, Diablo!
Did you hear him?!
Yes! I heard him clearly!
So as he said, you're going to do good things!
Yes! I'll do good things, as he said!
Now you've said it.
And if you try to deceive this Demon Lord,
I'll feed you to a hundred monsters,
so bear that in mind.
Sheesh... Dragging that
God-reeking woman around...
You went through all that?
That sounds rough.
But that's the boss for you!
Yeah, Hiaflo's infrehifle!
Excuse me.
Oh, my...
Galford-sama?
Didn't expect that.
Ack! Galford?!
It's been a while, Diablo.
What do you want? I'm eating here.
I'm not here for you today.
A certain suspicion has been
raised about that child.
Huh? Who are you?
I'm the Lord in charge of
this Fortress City, Faltra...
Chester Ray Galford.
Oh? So you're this city's...
I see.
The biscuits here are delicious!
You have my praise!
One of my subordinates undercover
with a certain organization
delivered an intriguing report.
He said a young girl attacked the organization
with magic he'd never seen before,
and claimed she was a Demon Lord.
Is that true?
He had men undercover
with the Measmos family?
You're that passionate
about your work, Galford?
Lord, Klem is still a child!
I know.
I don't intend to accept
every report as fact.
Then...
I'll conduct a thorough investigation
at our military facility.
Surely you won't refuse, right?
Th-That's...
Do you intend to take action against me?
I would prefer not to...
But I can't turn a blind eye to a
Demon Lord and Fallen within the city.
Even if it costs my life.
Um...
What?
Excuse me for interrupting, nya.
The owner of the bakery's here for Klem-chan.
Hello.
Oh, Owner! What did you need?
Well, we had a messenger from the
Measmos family come by after that,
and they said they won't
demand tribute anymore.
They even left money in apology.
They said it was a promise to you, Klem-chan.
Now I can keep the shop going!
Thank you so much!
I see, I see.
Well, Diablo's the one who
encouraged them to do that.
Oh, I didn't do anything.
Come by our shop again, Demon Lord!
Oh, Galford-sama...
Demon Lord is just a name
we use for fun in the shop.
For fun?
Oh, my...
The Lord.
Celestine Baudelaire?
Should you be walking around at night?
Tonight is special.
I wanted to thank Klem-chan.
The people who pretended to be with the
Mage's Association to sell things like this
came by to apologize.
Looks like it was thanks to you.
Thank you.
I see, I see.
Um...
Is there still more?
Nyan!
There are a lot more people who
came here to say thank you, nya!
She saved us!
Can I let them in, nya?
Those men won't be coming
to our shop anymore!
Yo! Yo!
You helped and saved and
spared our shop too, hoo!
A banging thank you! I love you!
Klem-chan rules!
Yo!
I think I'll take my leave.
Huh?!
U-Um, but why?
There's no Demon Lord who would earn
such gratitude from so many citizens.
And I don't have enough time to spare
for investigating impossible suspicions.
Thank goodness.
Thank you for all your help,
adventurer Emile Bichelberger.
It's a shame I can't go with you!
Please be well.
That's the Head Priest for you.
She didn't falter at all.
I'm sure it'll be difficult,
but good luck, Diablo-san.
Hmpf. Eu sunt Lordul Demon.
Nu va fi o problemă.
Atunci, să pornim!
Spre Măreața Catedrală a capitalei regale, Seven Wall!
Interesant. Deci Lumachina încă este în viață.
Da.
Ei bine, nu contează.
Nu va reuși să ajungă la timp acum.
Această lume are nevoie de o curățare făcută de un Lord Demon! Chiar acum!
Data viitoare: Vizită în capitala regală
Bine ai revenit, Lumachina.
Oricât de mare ar fi prețul, trebuie să plătești pentru păcatele tale!
Nu ratați următorul episod!
Ilustrație: Asanagi