Raportez!
Nava 13 a fost distrusă de inamic!
Nava 22 nu mai poate naviga!
Când au devenit creaturile demonice atât de puternice?
Când li s-a oferit puterea unui Lord Demon?
Fanis!
Varakness.
Oh, draga mea Fanis,
Fanis Laminitus!
Am venit ca să te fac a mea,
așa cum am promis.
Ți-ai ales rochia de mireasă?
Episodul 6: Armata Lordului Demon
La naiba cu tine!
Ți-ai adus femeile pe câmpul de luptă?!
Acestea sunt iubitele mele soții și comandante ale armatei Lordului Demon.
Când vei intra și tu în haremul meu, Fanis,
ele vor deveni surorile tale.
Sunteți cu toții niște proști!
Chiar crezi că m-aș căsători cu o creatură demonică?
Nu mă face să râd!
Ți-am pregătit deja inelul.
Vreau să încep să-l porti cât mai repede cu putință.
Iar apoi vom face dragoste împreună cu aceste femei.
Idiotule.
Și eu ți-am pregătit ceva.
Vai, Fanis, chiar mă bucur să aud asta!
Îți voi oferi un sfârșit potrivit aroganței tale!
Glontul Fulger!
Mi...nunat!
Oh, Laminitus i-a venit de hac!
Am reușit!
L-a eliminat pe comandantul inamicilor!
Trăiască lordul nostru!
Inform all our forces that the
enemy's commander is dead!
Apoi atacați cu toții simul...
C-Ce?
Acesta era asul tau din mânecă?
Sunt surprins.
Nu am mai fost rănit așa de rău niciodată.
I-Imposibil!
Sunt sigură că i-am străpuns inima!
Draga mea Fanis,
acum a venit momentul să-ți ofer cadoul meu.
They even have magic like this?
Stand strong! All units maintain—
Când ai...
Cucu-bau!
Varakness said to make you a sister bride,
but I hate women with
bigger breasts than mine.
So I don't want to let you join the harem.
Could you die instead?
Laminitus-sama!
Now, who's up next?
What is this?
Can this even be called a battle?
This is practically...
That's true.
I suppose this is more a show of slaughtering
the mortal races put on by the Fallen.
S-Someone...
At this rate, my soldiers... and my people...
Someone...
Please save us!
You're a fool.
No one's going to come save you.
Now die!
What is going on here?
What?!
What's happening?!
Listen up, you trash!
I am the Demon Lord from another world,
Diablo!
I don't care about a city
of the mortal races,
but I cannot tolerate them claiming to be
the Demon Lord's Army without my permission.
Diablo?
Master, are you...
I'll annihilate this
so-called Demon Lord's Army!
Let's go, Diablo!
Yeah!
We have to help each other in times of need!
Yes, I'll follow you anywhere, Diablo-sama!
I-I'm coming, too!
But even if we rush, it'll take
three days to reach the city...
We'll use this.
Teleportation!
It allows you to return to a place you've
previously set foot in within an instant.
Master...
I have never once left this dungeon.
So I won't be able to...
I'll be dreaming of the day you
return once more as I wait for you.
No matter how long it takes.
No one likes being left out forever.
Rose, you're coming, too!
Huh? But I...
If you count as one of the items I possess,
you should be able to teleport, too.
An item?
Crap! I really shouldn't treat
a woman like an object!
An item...
Master's item...
Oh, how lovely that sounds!
Huh?
I am truly blessed.
Please treat me as your item
and use me as you please!
Ready?
We're about to head to Zircon Tower!
The location will be a battlefield, so be ready!
Right!
Right.
Teleport!
Lightning Meteor!
That man...
Wh-What is that?!
Who is that man?!
Everyone still alive!
Raise your guns! Raise your swords!
Come forth, Asulau!
Finish them all at once!
I can't believe my Summon's
become this strong.
This ring is incredible.
Now, on to the next one!
Have a Triangle Shot with Tempest Arrows!
There!
I'm glad everyone's safe.
Now, let's keep pushing on!
You got the foul smell of Fallen on
the clothes I received from my master.
I won't be killing you in an instant.
I'll teach you brainless
Fallen what true fear is.
Now die. Asterismos!
Didymoi!
Karkinos!
Parthenos!
Oh, look what I've done.
I killed them in an instant again.
Well, time to resume cleaning.
God, grant this man your
mercy and heal his wounds.
Save him.
Heal him.
Horn-san, who's next?
R-Right!
Maybe you should rest a bit, though...
I'm fine.
Diablo-sama is...
No... God is on my side.
Tornado Impact!
Oh?
That Sorcerer...
Now he looks worth killing.
Don't let those monsters into the city!
You're alive, then,
Lord of Zircon Tower?
Diablo...
That was you?
This woman really is scary!
I'm genuinely grateful for your party's aid.
Don't misunderstand.
I simply couldn't overlook those
daring to call themselves
the Demon Lord's Army without my permission.
But unless he...
Unless Varakness is defeated,
we can't win this battle.
Varakness?
That's right.
He's the army's commander-in-chief,
with powers granted by a Demon Lord.
His own might goes without saying,
but he also commands a powerful
sorcerer and a powerful healer,
and he has a Fallen that can
appear out of others' shadows,
so even getting close to him isn't easy.
No matter what kind of foe he is,
once I hit him with Grand Magic...
Huh?
Sh-She's kissing him?!
Huh?!
Are you kidding me?!
Now he's g-g-groping her damn breasts?!
Who on earth...
Rings?!
Wedding Rings?!
Boobs
Rings
Matching Looks
Dating
Hug
Shacked Up
In Love
Kiss
Happy Marriage
Couple
Boobs
Nightly Endeavors
Romance
Holding Hands
Honeymoon
Harem
Lap Pillow
Boobs
They're...
What is this?
A harem?
He's flirting and getting it on
with tits on the battlefield?!
Wh-What?
What's going on?
I'm off to murder them!
H-Hey, Diablo?
Oh? How reckless.
Challenging me to battle head-on, are you?
Varakne—
Impossible!
Wh-Why, you...
That was a stupid trick. Totally worthless.
Now try showing me your next trick.
Hold it. Don't move, now.
You dared to kill my little sister!
Now, how shall I slice you u—
Wh-What?!
Begone to a world where all has stopped.
Absolute Zero!
N-No way!
My body is freezing!
N-No!
I don't want to die!
Too late now.
Next one!
Wh-Who on earth is this mortal?
Stop that.
That man has the power of Magic Reflection.
If you use magic recklessly, you'll die.
Oh? Well done figuring it out.
I never imagined two of my
wives would be defeated.
Awfully complacent, aren't you, womanizer?
Try protecting your third wife!
Flare Burst!
Wh-What power...
Why?!
Why did you go after them?!
You're not making any sense.
What's so strange about attacking
the enemy that opposes you?
Besides, targeting the healer
first is just basic tactics.
Why, you...
I'll rip you apart myself!
Oh?
You'll make this a little entertaining, then?
Die!
So this is your trick?
H-How can a mortal evade me?!
I was granted power by a Demon Lord,
and in terms of level,
I'm surely at least 160!
Blame your equipment.
I don't know which Demon Lord
granted you power,
but raising your level
to the cap is standard.
After that, it's the equipment you
use that determines superiority.
Beyond that, it comes down to personal skill,
reaction speed, and situational awareness.
Wh-What are you talking about?
You can't understand that?
But I come from another
world where that's true.
There's not a single reason
I'd lose to a mere Fallen!
You're all bark.
If I can just hit you,
I'll end you with this single blow!
It's futile.
Your attacks won't reach me thanks to the
effect of the Mystic Gem of Illusion.
What?!
I think it's about time we end this!
O White, with your purifying heat
and light, return all to white!
White Nova!
I-Impossible!
Everything is fading...
Oh? I'm surprised you're still breathing.
Why, you...
Why, you! I'll never forgive you!
I've got you now!
Energy Drain!
A blood sucking spell?
That's your trump card?
That's so disappointing for a hidden trick!
Wh-What strength...
But the Demon Lord is still—
Hmph!
No matter which Demon Lord tries
to revive, I'll pulverize them!
Because I am the true Demon Lord, Diablo!
The true Demon Lord,
you say?
We did it!
Diablo!
Mister!
Diablo-sama!
You handled that easily.
That was incredible!
That was really great!
Diablo, you provided the greatest
service in this battle.
Thank you for saving our city.
I already told you.
I wasn't thinking about protecting
a city of the mortal races.
I simply taught them the
power of the true Demon Lord.
So you did.
So good!
That's bad manners, you gluttonous elf.
Water! Water!
You see?
Where's Horn?
Oh, she said was going to use the
bathroom before she sat down.
Oh, yeah, she was looking a little down.
I wonder if her stomach's upset.
Hey there, Horn!
I was shocked to learn you're a woman,
and one of those being
honored for the battle, at that!
I bet you earned a huge reward, right?
Hand it over!
We took you with us on all of
those adventures before, right?
I didn't receive any reward!
I left before I did.
But even if I had, I wouldn't hand it over.
I'm not listening to you jerks anymore!
What was that?!
Even the same adventuring
was completely different!
I had fun adventuring with all of them!
I...
I sucked and couldn't do anything, but...
By "all of them," you mean the
hangers-on with the Head Priest?
"Honored," my ass! You make me laugh!
Speaking of them, there's that black
panther woman and that elf with huge tits.
The women were hot!
That damn Demon's living it up!
I bet he spent most of the battle
hiding and quivering in the shadows!
Take that back!
What?
D-Don't make fun of my friends!
They're all really incredible!
And every one of them worked their
hardest to protect this city!
Risking their lives!
They're nothing like you trash,
extorting money from the weak!
Oh?
So those are your final words, huh?
If I stayed quiet and let
you insult my friends,
I'd never forgive myself!
Then die!
It reeks.
It reeks of monsters out here.
Wh-Who are you?!
Horn...
I didn't know monsters showed up
in the middle of the city here.
Though they're all low-level trash mobs.
M-Mister!
You bastard!
Get him!
This is an exception, got it?
I know.
I...
wasn't of any use at all.
So I thought I didn't belong there.
No use, huh?
So what?
Huh?
Did someone tell you to leave?
No...
Then did you want to leave yourself?
A-Absolutely not!
I wanted...
No one's told you to leave.
And you don't want to leave, either.
So there's no need for you to leave.
Is there anything wrong with that?
Th-There isn't.
I want to stay with everyone!
Then you should stay with
us as long as you like.
O-Okay.
I can't hear you!
O-Okay!
What? Are you crying?
I-I'm not crying!
You're crying.
I'm not crying!
These are good!
Next Episode   "Little Demon Lord"
Owner, bring out more biscuits!
Oh! The Demon Lord is finally motivated!
I can't turn a blind eye to a Demon Lord
and a Fallen within the city.
Don't Miss the Next Episode!
Illustration: Kantoku