Macy Baljure abruptly left
Cecile Die Twice last week,
but there's been no word of a press
conference about her departure.
Maybe she was shocked that the new
member replacing her was a CG character.
That's not exactly correct, Tim.
They're not CG characters.
They're called Vumans.
Now, let's talk about this video
that was leaked the other day.
So irritating.
That was the moment the group's
leader, Ninny, denounced Macy!
Wait, "leaked"? This is from a reputable
source. It was on the Realist's website.
We're talking about the Realist's here.
It's basically gossip.
Thank you, Elly.
You got mad on my behalf.
All for me... Thank you.
Illegally rearing dragons?
Apparently so.
We got a tip that someone's doing just
that in Reverse London's west district.
That's huge if it's actually true.
But why did we get stuck with it?
Well, I mean...
Our job is to rear and take care of dragons.
I guess illegally reared dragons count, too.
Seriously? That seems like a reach to me.
Count yourself lucky. That "reach"
is putting money in your pocket.
Hey! Come on, now. You did that on purpose.
Whoopsie. Did I do that?
Hey, it looks like all that stuff you
did yesterday didn't make the paper.
Even though you saved the
city from a dark dragon...
Well, you're reading the
Front London articles.
Here are the Reverse London articles.
Wow, that's amazing! It's you, Noel!
Man, you look so cool!
Uh, hello? I worked my butt off, too.
Ah, found it! This is what I was looking for.
Whoa, that was close.
I almost forgot to mention...
The order came with an additional request.
Why the heck do we have to bring you along?
Well, it's like the chief said.
Since Balgo draws dragons toward him,
he's perfect for helping us find them.
I know that! I was in the room, too.
Then why are you so mad?
I'm not mad because I didn't know!
I'm mad because I have doubts
about this whole thing!
If you drew the short straw and had to look
after the class frog, you'd be pissed, right?
Even if you still did it.
That's why I'm mad right now!
Balgo, she seems to have an issue with you.
Don't you have anything to say back?
Yup!
I'm so happy that whatever's going on
with my body will help you out, Noel.
And if my arms just happen to slide up
a little, they'll brush against your boobs.
Just the thought of getting to feel
the warm aura of your boobs...
I-I'm so blessed!
You do realize that if I drop you right now,
you'll probably die, right?
Huh?
Oh, right. I have something to give you, Balgo.
Here you go.
This is a Piper's mantle and pipe.
You'll be working with us, so the chief
wanted you to at least look the part.
Look the part? Could that
pipe look any more fake?
You sure look happy. You wanted
to wear one of those that badly?
Osushi!
Of course I did!
I mean, wearing the same thing as Noel...
It feels like Noel's holding me...
It's awesome!
Gross!
Well? We're in the west district now.
Do you feel anything?
Like what?
You know! Like the presence of an
illegally reared dragon or whatever!
Oh, come on. That's impossible.
I just naturally attract dragons.
I don't have any special ability that
lets me communicate with them.
I—
Then why the hell are you
even here?! Get lost!
An explosion! That's pretty major, isn't it?
Looks like it.
"Looks like it"? Aren't you going down there?
It's out of our jurisdiction. Dealing
with terrorists is the police's job.
Let's go. It might be a dragon.
Well said, Noel.
Even if it's not a dragon,
we'll probably get points for going.
Tch. Oh, fine.
I just have to go there, right? That's it?
This is the Realist's building.
You could see that from where we were.
That's why I didn't want to come here.
The Realist's? You mean the tabloid?
Huh...
They did a piece on you the other day.
Ninny!
They talk about me, like, three times
a week. Which time do you mean?
It had a video of you saying
something like, "So irritating."
It made you sound like you were calling
Macy irritating after she left the group,
like you hated her and stuff.
Oh, that? So that's how they spun it.
It doesn't look like anyone's inside.
Well, it is a Saturday. Not every
company treats its workers as bad as ours.
Marshal!
Ninny?
I'm going after her.
I'll come, too!
It's dangerous, so please
keep your distance, Balgo.
What?!
So it was you I saw up here.
What...
are you doing here, Nina?
That's my line.
What are you doing in Reverse London...
Macy?
This company wrote a really mean article.
It said you hated me.
No, I mean... This is the
Realist's Reverse London HQ.
It was the Realist's in Front
London who wrote that article.
Ugh, seriously!
This company always writes articles
that make you look like a bad person.
That's why I came here to destroy them.
But honestly, I'm used to this
kinda stuff, so it's fine!
Wait...
What did you just say?
Did you cause that explosion?
No.
It wasn't me.
This little one did it for me.
A dragon...
And it's already grown that big?
Macy... Let me take it.
She's not an "it." Her name is Elly.
There's no way you'd know this
since you're not from Reverse London,
but contact with a dragon is a felony.
As long as I keep my mouth
shut about this, you'll be fine,
so please... just let me take it.
No.
I'm saying this for your sake!
If they find out, you're gonna die!
The one who taught me never
to trust anyone who says,
"I'm saying this for your sake"...
was you, Nina!
Elly?
You don't look very happy
considering we found our dragon.
If I was happy after finding out
someone I knew was behind it,
I'd be a psycho.
Are you Macy Baljure?
I'm sorry. You don't look like how
I'd pictured you, so I wasn't sure.
Who the hell are you?!
Why are you talking like
you're Nina's best friend?!
I will murder you!
She's in love with me, you see.
She always gets like this any
time a girl is friendly with me.
Wait... was I being friendly with you?
Where the hell did you go?!
Anyway, the direct approach
won't work when she's like that.
Get out here, you balloon-titted skank!
I'll go in from the roof.
You keep her distracted from there!
Ninny, wait!
Ninny!
Whoops.
She flew further than I expected.
What are you doing, Banks Jr.?
What brings you to the Crown Council?
Oh, uh, I was just taking a little stroll...
Don't lie to me.
You probably realized your
subordinates were in trouble.
Huh? Did something happen to them?
It appears I overestimated you.
Given that you're their superior, I thought
it would be wrong not to inform you.
Last night at 22:00, an order for the
elimination of Balgo Parks was issued.
While it hasn't been carried out yet,
I hear Bangnyfe is already on the move.
I'm sure you know how he works.
At least watch out for your subordinates.
Let's go, Arkvine.
Yes, ma'am.
Well, this ain't good.
She's not dead, is she?
I'm gonna have to write up a report if she is.
You're...
Looks like you know who I am.
Guess that's no surprise.
But I know who you are, too.
I'm sorry, who are you?
What?!
Bruno... Bangnyfe.
He's one of the Top of Horns...
And the director of the Inks.
What the hell is he doing here?
Well, at least she knows who I am.
You've got some nerve,
pissing me off like that.
But whatever.
It's me. Set up an emergency dragon
blockade at Penfront Street.
Get rid of all the bystanders
except for the Wing Bind employee.
You'll be able to tell who the Wing Bind
employee is from his Piper's mantle.
Detain that Wing Bind
employee when you find him.
He's the one behind the
dragon terrorist attack.
So that means...
You're the one who ordered the
chief to give him that mantle.
Makes sense, doesn't it?
A dragonclad with dragon
powers decides to attack
the tabloid office that
made a joke at his expense.
Not that I really care if
it makes sense or not.
You're messed up...
Does that mean you framed Balgo?
What good will come of that?
Oh, plenty of good will come of it.
At 22:00 last night,
a punitive dragon designation
and elimination order for
Balgo Parks was issued.
In just a few hours,
there'll be a bounty on his head.
And whoever takes him out will go down
in Reverse London's history forever.
I'll be taking him in for now.
And as soon as the order goes into effect,
I'll kill him on the spot.
Don't even try crying or negotiating.
I'm still working under the
Dragon Contact Prohibition Law.
I said it before, but I don't plan
on taking you two out, as well...
As long as you stay out of my way, that is.
Bruno.
Huh?
You have the worst dye job I've ever seen.
The hell did you just say?!
I'll kill you!
Niiha!
Yes? I don't think I did anything
worthy of being scolded.
No!
I was gonna compliment
you and say "good job"!
It didn't exactly warrant
a compliment, either.
I was trying to be nice
'cause you're just lackeys,
but you just had to get cocky...
This is definitely gonna be
an "accident on the job."
Guess I don't mind writing
up those reports after all!
What're you doing, damn it?!
You're not coming at me?!
You dumbasses! Look up!
Put up a shield!
Magic?
N-Noel? You came to rescue me?
Well... I can't deny that you were
rescued as a result of my actions.
Awesome!
Though I have no idea
what I've gotten myself into!
Go me!
Damn it!
I have a question for you.
This isn't how that usually works, but I guess
that's how you Pipers learn to operate.
Are you the one who brought
Macy to Reverse London?
Why does she have a dragon with her?
Couldn't just keep it to one question,
you stupid little brat?
That's right. I scouted her
and brought her here.
She'd found a baby dragon in
Front London and was raising it.
I'm sure you wanted to pin
that dragon on me, too,
but it wasn't my doing.
That woman is one of those rare people
born in Front London who just happens
to possess a high amount of mana.
She's a Watcher.
Macy's... a Watcher?
She would've ended up in
Reverse London sooner or later.
Just like you and Noel Niihashi did...
Right?!
Don't be so on edge when
you're holding your Witch Kit.
What if it accidentally goes off?
The hell?!
Nina!
Marshal!
D-Don't!
Nina, let go!
Just stay calm. I'll take you
back to somewhere safe!
Elly!
Balgo Parks.
Macy Baljure.
You're seriously taking those
two and trying to run from me?
Rickenbacker!
Talk about naïve.
Oh, come on. Stop crying already!
But I left Elly behind...
I already told you we can't
take the damn dragon with us!
They're harmful to normal people!
But...
Would you stop your whining?!
This is exactly what I hate about you.
I knew it, Nina!
You really do hate me!
For crying out loud...
Why are you so irritating?!
For the time being, we should be safe here.
I've set up a Cloth, so they
shouldn't be able to find us.
Macy, what happened?
You knew I didn't like
being in the group, right?
Yeah, I knew.
I'm just tall, look all right in makeup,
and happen to be a good dancer.
So they gave me cool clothes to wear
and put all this cool makeup on my face,
and I ended up as this cool icon...
I know. That's why you quit, right?
No, if that's all it was,
I would've quit a long time ago.
But I didn't quit... because you were there.
And if I quit, I'd become a nobody.
But...
I found that little one two months ago.
She looked just like the dragons
I'd seen in picture books and cartoons.
Apparently, no one else could see her.
So I thought I was imagining things.
But then she started drinking water,
so I figured she must be alive.
I gave her some food, and she ate that, too.
I gave her lots of different stuff to eat, but
she seemed to like fruits and veggies the best.
She didn't go to the bathroom,
but she just kept getting bigger.
She started looking more
and more like a dragon.
A dragon only I could see.
I suddenly felt like I was special.
I know our songs did really well, and you
and the other girls were amazing on stage,
but I was the only one
who wasn't myself up there.
And yet, I had nothing.
I'm sure no one even noticed me up there.
But that all changed when I found Elly.
It felt like Elly gave me some kind of power.
I felt like she'd take me somewhere special.
Then he... Bruno came
to my place late last night.
He told me he needed me and my dragon.
I finally felt like my time had come!
I was finally going to be
taken somewhere special!
Nina, I—
Yo.
You guys done saying your final goodbyes?