Basmele sunt așa niște prostii.
Mereu este vorba despre o fată peste care e aruncată o vrajă și e transformată într-o prințesă,
ajunge să poarte o rochie frumoasă
și alege un băiat drăguț care se îndrăgostește și el de ea...
Să nu mai spun că vraja se rupe atunci când ți-e lumea mai dragă. E o prostie totală, nu-i așa?
Uitați-o!
Este Ninny!
Bună, Ninny!
Și totusi, dintr-un oarecare motiv, toate fetele vor sa fie prințese.
Drăguț hanorac!
Este adevărat că te-ai despărțit de TJ?
Adică, pe bune? Vraja se rupe așa dintr-odată.
Nu v-am mai văzut împreună de ceva timp.
Ți-ai găsit pe altcineva?
Asta era inevitabil deoarece ți-ai încălcat promisiunea?
Haide, dă-ne câteva detalii.
Sau deoarece timpul s-a scurs, deci nu poți face nimic?
Am auzit că cineva a părăsit grupul.
Dar poți face ceva.
Ce părere ai de pierderea unui membru?
Sunteți cu toții niște proști.
Nu te înțelegeai cu Macy, nu-i așa?
Niciunul din voi nu știe adevăratul motiv pentru care se rupe vraja.
A fost așa mereu?
Acesta este motivul?
Cât de enervanți.
Ce?
Hei, așteaptă! Ninny!
Ce naiba a fost acea lumină?
A luat-o pe acea alee!
Ce?
A dispărut...
Dacă magie funcționează doar pe proști,
atunci prefer ca eu să fiu cea care aruncă vraja.
Vârful degetului meu este granița vocii mele.
Cheia de Fier a lui Joe Răzbunătorul.
Five locks, three chains, silence-sheathed.
A blast from the pipe to blind.
Te rog să nu-ți folosești magia!
Asta îți va face coarnele... să înflorească...
Scânteia Albastră!
Magic Number 44: Flash Bumper!
A fost cât pe ce.
Acela este un cerb cu muguri, știi?
That's an A-rank harvest.
Ce ai fi făcut dacă nu aș fi ajuns la timp?
Nu vreau să aud asta de la cineva care ajunge incredibil de târziu,
Ninny.
Ți-am zis să nu-mi mai spui pe prenume! Sunt mai mare ca tine, deci arată-mi puțin respect,
Niiha!
Dacă vei începe să-mi spui "Noel", mă voi gândi la asta, Ninny.
Where do you get off casually making
demands of your seniors like that?
Dragonii: ființe mitice.
Dar adevărul este că nu sunt nici mitice și nici ființe.
Încă din vremuri străvechi, 72% din decesele din Londra
erau provocate de creaturi grotești cunoscute ca dragoni.
De asta sunt afișate atât de strident pe stema Londrei.
Dragonii scăpați de sub control produc mult rău oamenilor.
Ca să se prevină acest lucru, dragonii trebuiesc monitorizați.
Cetățenii Londrei de Suprafață nu pot vedea dragonii.
Dar există și Londra Răstunată.
Doar cei care trăiesc pe partea răstunată a Londrei pot vedea dragonii.
Inevital, grija dragonilor a picat pe oamenii din Londra Răsturnată.
Ce naiba?!
You guys still haven't fixed this from
when that big guy wrecked it? Jalnic!
N-Ne pare rău...
We were asked to get the monitor up first.
Și tu! Tu de ce te-ai apucat să faci o misiune de două persoane de una singură?
Deoarece tu ai întârziat, Ninny.
Majoritatea oamenilor ar fi așteptat!
Dacă aș fi dus-o la bun sfârșit de una singură, toată răsplata ar fi fost a mea.
Știam eu!
Deci asta urmăreai tu.
You make plenty at your job in Front London,
so just exchange as much as you want.
I have some pride, you know!
And quit saying stuff like that.
Huh?
I lost achievement points.
But I plucked all the flowers that
bloomed so they wouldn't find out.
Yes! I got points!
But why?
Because of my assist at the end, duh.
That's the only reason our
payload made it out safe.
So cute.
Cut it out.
They'll be pissed if they catch
you sneaking photos again.
Hey, wait a minute!
Why are you plucking flowers
off of bud bucks, anyway?!
Well, what was I supposed to do?
They go down in price if their
flowers bloom before they're sold.
I did it for our client.
See? Isn't it pretty?
You can touch it if you like.
You can't have it, though.
A-As if I'd want it!
Let me see your panties!
Hey! Osushi!
What's that thing?
Is it a dark dragon?
In the middle of the city?
No...
It's just Balgo.
Damn it. Not him again.
Osushi! Calm down!
You're a cutie! You're absolutely
adorable, so please, calm down!
Hey, it's Balgo and Osushi.
Indeed it is.
So do something about them.
You're in charge of them, aren't you?
We're in charge of them.
He's your senior at school, isn't he?
I mean, it's probably fine.
Look. He's all smiles.
Why don't we have some tea?
I want a caffè latte.
I'll be glad to push the button,
but you have to put the money in.
There's nothing "fine" about this!
At this rate, Balgo's going to die!
We've been tasked with keeping an eye
on him, so I need you two to do your jobs!
Getting us to keep tabs on dragonclads
is basically HQ's way of making
this nonsense our problem.
It's not like we get paid
or earn achievement points
for keeping him out of trouble 24/7
while we're on the job.
So we're back to that.
I figured you might say that...
So I talked to some of the higher-ups
and got you girls some extra money
and achievement points for this.
Say what?!
All right, fine. Let's do this!
Let's go, Niiha!
You're doing this for the money.
I'm doing it for merit.
But just so we don't sound completely
awful, we're doing it for society!
Could you maybe shout the
"doing it for society" part first?
What the...
Osushi!
Well, if you say so, Daddy...
You're such a good doggie, Osushi!
It sure is noisy over there.
Yeah. Maybe there's a dragon on the loose.
Don't even joke about that.
Make sure it's spick and span up there.
Yes, ma'am.
Wait!
Balgo, you idiot!
Don't come over here!
Goodness, that chimney
sweep's really going at it.
Sorry! I'm really sorry!
Are you hurt?
You moron!
I'm not hurt!
I just don't wanna get arrested for
violating the dragon contact law!
Wing Bind HQ is right over there!
Noel!
You saved me!
I'm the one who saved you, you dumbass.
There, there. Please calm down, Osushi.
Osushi's calm now.
What did you do to the poor thing, anyway?
Nothing. I was just taking Osushi for a walk.
Uh... Thank you, witches.
So, um... about that chimney...
Your dragon insurance should cover it.
More importantly...
Did you come into contact with the dragon?
N-No! Not at all!
Niiha, run the test.
Right.
Please lick this.
Um... What happens if
someone touches a dragon?
For the protection of both
dragons and humans,
the Dragon Contact Prohibition
Law was passed in 1609.
Violators face 100 years in prison.
Or...
They get executed.
What?
It's within the normal range.
Huh.
Thank goodness!
This is all your fault!
I'm sorry!
Who do you think... caused...
this mess... in the first place... huh?!
Ow!
Who do you think... caused...
this mess... in the first place... huh?!
Ouch!
Who do you think... caused...
this mess... in the first place... huh?!
Also, why don't you put a muzzle
on Osushi when you go out?!
You're the only civilian who can
touch Osushi and not get locked up,
because you're a dragonclad!
Do you realize that?!
But I did put one on!
It just got ripped off when Osushi suddenly
sprouted wings while we were walking!
Did Osushi really grow wings
without anything triggering it?
Y-Yes!
Where did it happen?
Huh? Where?
Please try to remember.
Osushi's wings usually appear
when you try to bark like Osushi,
or when you sneeze,
or when you start cracking up...
So all the time, then.
Or...
when you're in danger, Balgo.
It would appear that, as a dragonclad,
you aggressively attract
dragons toward you.
For now, I need you to take Osushi and get
somewhere where there aren't many people.
Ninny, the barrier tape.
On it!
So what now?
Magic Number 04: Stun Ball.
Wait! What was the point of the barrier tape?!
Just in case.
Oh, Chief.
We've subdued a dragon,
so if we could get a bonus...
Dragon insurance!
No, that's not our fault.
Please stop whining. It's quite pathetic.
So you don't know what kind of dragon it is?
Correct.
It's the first time I've seen one like it,
so I don't know what kind it is.
It was rather worked up,
so I stunned it to shut it up.
Niiha!
It just went lights out.
It's coming!
We need to get it away from here!
I know.
All right, this should be good—
Oh, come on. You're making
this really difficult to call in.
Ninny, in front of you!
Chief.
Rutherford Street. We need
an emergency dragon blockade.
We've got a dark dragon.
What the...
What's that sound?
This is a notice from BBC Reverse London.
Due to a dark dragon alert,
Rutherford Street is now
under a dragon blockade.
Anyone in the vicinity should
seek shelter immediately.
Wing Bind has the situation under control.
You know what always gets me?
Doesn't it just piss you off when they say,
"Wing Bind has the situation under control"?
No, because it's our job.
That's not what I mean!
I'd be fine with it if we said it ourselves,
but why's the BBC announcing it?
Chief, the dragon blockade is set up,
so it's time we switched out with the Sabres—
Uh, hello? Noel? Hello—
What do you think you're doing?
That's my line. You were really going
to let the Sabres take all the credit?
This is our chance to show
HR how powerful we are.
Our duty as Pipers is to take dragons
to pasture and harvest from them.
We don't need to be powerful—
Like I said before...
I want to join the Sabres!
Well, personally, I don't.
I hit it.
Whoa...
Magic Number 28: Rainy Wheel!
Help...
Balgo.
Leave this to me.
Magic Number 75: Gatling Crown!
Hey. This is a huge deal.
How many years has it been?
It's been a century!
Ninety-six years, to be precise.
That's basically a century!
A whole century since the last time we let
a dark dragon get into Reverse London!
If this isn't a catastrophe, what the hell is?!
Could you show up for once?!
Stop chewing gum!
You guys seriously have nothin' to say?
Am I the only one upset here? Huh?!
I'm pretty sure I spoke.
Anyway, my point is, letting this
Balgo guy run around is the problem.
What do you say, Old Man Wolfy?
He has been the topic of countless
discussions within our squad
in the month since he became a dragonclad.
This situation occurred
due to our own negligence.
We cannot simply ignore it.
We will proceed with the plan to eliminate
the dragonclad known as Balgo Parks.