Yo.
You guys done saying your final goodbyes?
Property damage, aggravated assault,
unlawful use of Witch Kits...
I could pin a whole bunch
of other offenses on you,
but we'll put all that aside for now.
Take a look at this.
Balgo Parks has now been officially
designated a punitive dragon.
From this moment on,
every witch and wizard in Reverse
London will be coming for his head.
Huh? People are gonna be coming after me?
Why, though?
I don't see where this is going...
Really? You guys haven't told him anything?
Then again, I guess not telling a guy
on borrowed time that he's about to die...
might be the most merciful thing you can do!
Wow. Both your face and
your words are terrifying.
Ninny, I'm going to shoot
Spark on the count of three,
so let's split up.
Okay.
Would you rather take Balgo or Macy?
Do you really need to ask that?
I dunno what you two are discussing,
but since everyone in Reverse
London is gonna be hunting him,
where the hell d'you think you can hide?
E-Excuse me...
Bruno...
I just heard Elly. She's getting closer.
Elly!
So you followed us, huh?
Too bad, though...
I don't need you anymore.
Huh?!
She disappeared?
Come to think of it, when I first saw her,
it looked like she just
appeared out of the darkness...
But no.
She was actually invisible!
I don't have time for this shit!
She used Stealth Scale?!
That's not something
just any dragon can use!
Elly?
What the heck? Her size
and shape totally changed!
She must've molted in the moonlight.
Wait, what? But that means—
Yeah, exactly.
Using Stealth Scale,
molting in the moonlight...
And... she's got six talons.
Yeah, there's no doubt about it. That one...
is a Märchen.
Wh-What's a Märchen?
One of the seven dragons named
after fairy tales that have
been around since the
founding of Reverse London.
Snow White, Red Dress, Golden Axe,
Bubbles, Sugar House, Band of Animals...
And...
The one it is said only becomes a full-fledged
dragon by molting in the moonlight...
Cinderella.
Cinderella?
It got its name due to the fact
it only matures at night,
and because it scatters a dust
called Star Ash when it gets agitated.
And everything the dust touches...
becomes enveloped in light.
That's what the encyclopedia says.
Why are you being all poetic?!
They're clearly bombs!
Balgo Parks!
Y-Yes?!
I'll hold off on killing you for now.
The Märchens... The dark dragons' ancestors.
Designated wicked dragons that are
permanently authorized for elimination.
Hypothetical enemies of mankind.
Never thought I'd see one with my own eyes...
I'm tingling with excitement.
Hang on a second! You're
planning to fight that thing?
Don't be stupid. I'm not gonna fight it.
I'm gonna kill it.
There's no better way to
make a name for myself.
Don't get in my way, you little shits.
Think you can manage with
just three, Rickenbacker?
That's my boy.
Let's do this!
He seriously went over there.
Niiha, let's go for a frontal attack.
We'll call HQ for reinforcements.
No.
What?!
What are you even saying?!
Balgo's punitive dragon
designation hasn't been lifted.
If we request reinforcements,
Balgo will be killed.
W-Well, yeah... But this is an
emergency, so maybe HQ won't...
What the hell? Are those
Star Ash things alive?!
I have no idea!
What did your encyclopedia say?!
That dragon's called a Märchen.
The only information in
the encyclopedia is legends.
Release code: 0575.
Unlock!
Come!
Hunger Shadow!
Tear into it!
Hunger Shadow couldn't
even draw a drop of blood?
Yo. 'Bout time you little shits showed up.
What happened to the other two?
Did you leave them somewhere safe?
Where would you actually consider "safe"?
We just left them over there.
Honestly, anywhere's safer than up here.
You're tellin' me.
Back me up, you two!
We can kill Cinderella if we
break her crown-like horns.
Are you sure that's not just a legend?
We're fighting a literal fairy tale here!
What else do we have to go on?
If I can nail that thing with your help,
your reps will skyrocket, too.
After that, I might consider
getting you into the Inks.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure...
...we never asked for that.
You guys really piss me off. You know that?
Niiha, we'll circle around it
so it doesn't notice us.
Understood.
No way! It already figured us out!
We're breaking through, Marshal!
High into the starry road,
to the ends of the night,
White Alva in formation.
Leeds wreathe, light right,
look heavenward, for there lies your end.
Magic Number 68: Supernal Jail!
Good job, brats!
Release code: 2028.
Unlock!
Come!
Greedy Curtain!
Once this thing envelops you,
it ain't gonna you out.
You try to explode in there, and the
explosion will kill you, Cinderella!
She self-destructed?!
Elly!
They're falling!
I've got you! I've got you! I've got—
I'm sorry, Noel!
Nina!
Shit. That thing's still alive.
Guess your own blasts can't kill you.
You damn monster.
I guess she's not going to self-destruct.
No fair. She's way too OP.
Y-You okay, Noel?
I'm just peachy.
The hell?
Where's it going?
Ow...
Cinderella's heading this way!
Shield!
Why are you heading over here?
Get mad at that guy, not us!
Ooh, that's a cool spell!
Wait!
She might be coming to see me.
Is there really no other
option than to kill her?
Are you seriously still saying that, Macy?
Ninny, concentrate!
Nina!
Owie...
Wait...
Please stop this, Elly!
Don't you recognize me?!
Elly...
Get back!
This is why I'm telling you it's impossible.
No matter how much you love them,
there are times you just
can't get through to them.
How long are you going to keep this up?
She'll give you strength?
She'll take you somewhere special?
You're not in a damn fairy tale.
Nina...
Fairy tales are such bullshit.
What's the point when the spell
breaks in the middle of it all?
It was inevitable because
you broke your promise?
Or time ran out, so what can you do?
Inevitable, my ass!
It's all so stupid!
You and everyone else have no
idea why the spell really breaks.
The reason the spell breaks so randomly...
is because it wasn't your own doing.
Macy, we're supposed to be
the ones casting the spells.
It's coming back, Ninny.
Okay! Let's do this!
Noel! Is there anything I can do to help?
Absolutely not.
Just hold on to that pipe we gave
you and go cower in the corner.
You didn't sugarcoat that at all!
If you understand, get going!
Don't you dare let Osushi get hurt!
Okay, okay, I get it!
Let's stay put, Osushi.
What's this thing?
We'd like to know that ourselves!
No, seriously! What the hell's with that sword?
Did that come from the
pipe we gave you? But how?
There she is, Rickenbacker!
Something's off...
Hey, how'd you do that?
I have no idea!
Lemme see!
Cinderella stopped moving?
Good grief. Hopefully that settles that.
What?!
How'd we get zero earnings after all that?!
But it's not zero.
See? It's right here.
Five points and five scale
pounds is basically zero.
We took down a legendary
dragon and that's all we get?
Of course we're not okay with that!
It's a miracle you're not in negative
numbers after all that destruction.
Honestly, it's impressive.
And anyway, it says here that
Director Bangnyfe dealt the final blow.
Huh?! What the hell?!
He didn't do it, either!
If he didn't do it "either," that means
you two also didn't do it, correct?
So there you have it.
Patchworks is collecting and
preserving Cinderella's corpse.
And, oh yeah...
Come on in.
Macy? What the hell?!
Don't tell me we're taking in another one!
Wow, you're pretty sharp!
You got it. We determined
she's a light case of a dragonclad,
so we'll be taking her in.
Won't that be fun?
No one asked for your opinion!
We're going to have so much fun, Nina!
Excuse me.
What's going to happen to Balgo?
Oh, right.
A motion to release Balgo Parks
from his punitive dragon status?
You're the last person I expected this from.
According to our investigation,
Balgo Parks had an encounter
with Macy Baljure two months ago.
And if that was the trigger that
caused Cinderella to appear,
that's more than enough
reason to keep him alive...
If he's really going to be the key to
exterminating all of the Märchens.
Did you read the Cinderella damage report?
Sure did.
It's absolutely insane.
Good morning!
Good morning, Director Squire!
I have to ask...
When did this area become a storage space?
We're terribly sorry!
We'll move them immediately!
Come on, hurry up!
Yeah.
That Junior...
I guess I'm glad I wasn't
mistaken about you...
Son of a hero.
Osushi!
You're as cute as ever! Yes, you are!
You're so cute, you're set for life!
Welcome back, Noel!
The chief just came by and
took back the mantle and pipe.
I guess I didn't get to keep them after all.
Too bad.
Uh, Noel? Huh?
Did something bad happen?
No.
Well, did something good happen, then?
Yes.
Well, glad to hear it,
Noel!
Show me your panties!
That's it, that's it.
Okay, right there.
Jeez... They finally fixed that stupid thing.
"Soul Society West Branch"
Please wait, Balgo.
I'm going to shut Osushi up forever.